Cease fire! Cease fire! Heads up!
停止射擊！停止射擊！抬起頭！
Man down! Cease fire!
有人中彈，停火
(echoes): Stupid motherfucker!
笨蛋！
What's up, Sylvia?
西維亞，最近怎麼樣？
Cute little outfit.
小套裝好可愛
You look nice.
你看上去很漂亮
Mike's in the bedroom.
邁克在睡房
Yeah?
是嗎？
Man, I said you look nice.
哎，我說你看上去很漂亮
I have a court appearance, Jim.
我穿的可是禮服，吉姆
Well, you just give 'em hell.
呵，你可是一點也不配合
Hey.
嘿
Spiffy duds, huh?
很有派頭吧？
You look like a gift-wrapped turd.
你看上去像包裝好的垃圾
Now please leave me alone. I have to concentrate.
現在請讓我靜一下，我必須集中精神
I have two filings and a deposition today.
我今天要進行兩項申報和一項取證
Play nice, kids.
朋友，玩得開心嗎？
What up, dog?
你好啊，老兄
- Nothing. Just got back. - Cool. Cool.
- 沒什麼，剛剛回來 - 不錯
How was Mexico, dog?
墨西哥那邊怎麼樣，老兄？
Oh, it was a dream, man.
哦，就像一個夢，朋友
- Loving my woman. - Right.
- 我愛我的女人 - 不錯
That's it. I'm out of here.
都在這裡，我出去了
Those are copies of your resume.
這些是你簡歷的複印件
Pass them out like candy.
就像發糖果一樣把它們發出去 因為我隨時可以再印多一點出來
And just call me if anything happens, okay?
如果有什麼事情就給我電話，好嗎？
And no drinking.
還有，不要喝酒
Come on, baby, be cool.
來吧，寶貝，放鬆下
Honey, I'm serious.
親愛的，我可是認真的
No drinking. Okay?
不要喝酒，好嗎？
- I love you. - I love you, too.
- 我愛你 - 我也愛你
Good luck.
祝你好運
Your suit's fine, okay?
你的衣服很不錯，行了吧？
Dude, she called me a gift-wrapped turd.
老兄，她把我叫做包裝過的垃圾
Don't be fucking with her, dude.
不要招惹她，老兄
She's pissed.
她生氣了
Why is she on the warpath? Dog...
- 她為什麼氣那麼不順？ - 老兄…
I didn't look for work yesterday, dude.
老兄，昨天我沒有找工作
Sold some of her CDs, bought a couple of 40s
賣掉一些她的CD，買40盎司酒
and a pack of GPCs.
和一包廉價煙
Caught a buzz and watched
打了個電話
my Chicago vs. Lakers tapes.
然後觀看我那盤芝加哥對湖人隊的帶子
(laughs): That's on you, homie.
兄弟，這才像你
We didn't even hang yesterday.
我們昨天還沒出去玩過呢
I was out of the country.
我出國去了
So? My old lady still thinks it's your fault.
然後？我老婆還堅持 認為這是你的錯呢
Huh? Huh? Hmm?
嗯？嗯？嗯？
Come on, dude, let's get the fuck out of here
來吧，老兄，我們離開這裡
and find my ass some employment.
去找點活幹
It's cool you driving me around?
你開車帶我兜一圈爽一下？
Yeah, dude, it's cool. It's no trouble.
耶，老兄，這樣爽，沒問題
JIM: Here, asshole.
朋友，這裡
Breakfast.
給你早飯
Oh... ho, ho...
噢，呵呵…
Dog.
老兄
No pisto for me, dude.
老兄，我不喝啤酒
Today's a no-pounding day. You heard the woman.
你沒聽那個女士說嗎？ 今天是禁酒日
Good. More for me.
好，我喝多點
Fuck it.
去他的
Salud.
- 乾杯
Man, hope they put me in the next class or I'm fucked.
夥計，希望他們能夠把我放在下一班 要不我就慘了
I can't pay my rent.
我連房租都交不起了
Landlady's about to pull a gauge on my ass.
房東老太準備拿槍轟我了
What happened to all that money you saved in the army, dude?
老兄，你在軍隊服役時候攢的錢去那裡了？
The tax-free shit?
免繳稅的錢？
Man, bro, this fucking ride cleaned me out.
夥計，我花光在這這該死的車子上了
I guess we drank up the rest.
我猜我們把剩下的錢都喝光了
(chuckles): Dumb ass.
別說了
Cops better start paying you, dude.
警察局最好立刻僱用你，老兄
You spend enough fucking time with them.
你對他們花了夠多的時間了
They better start kicking me down some paychecks, man.
他們最好馬上給我開支票，朋友
They got me hopping through hoops, you know?
你知道嗎？他們跟我兜圈子
"Come in for a test." "Come back in two weeks."
「來做個測試」，「兩周後再來」
Another test, another two weeks.
又一個測試，再來個兩周
Fuck.
去他的
Shit gets real,
當討厭的事情變得真實
you be hating life.
你就會討厭生活
Party time will be over.
開心的時間快結束了
Dude, you don't know how much
老兄，你對這個不是很瞭解
I'm looking forward to this shit.
我期待著這份工作
You know, I'll be super recruit.
你知道嗎？我會成為超級尖兵
I was jumping out of choppers
我從直升機上面
in the mountains, taking down
跳到大山裡面
hard motherfuckers, you know?
幹掉那些難纏的壞蛋，你知道嗎？
I'll be laughing my way through LAPD's reindeer games.
我會笑著通過洛杉磯警察局的考核
Shit, they're gonna love me.
呵，他們將喜歡我的
Yeah, yeah, you're gonna fucking love them, dude.
耶，耶，你也會喜歡他們的，老兄
Ah, fuck you.
哦，去你的吧
I'm going to love my old lady.
我要去愛我老婆
I'm gonna marry homegirl.
我將和那個女孩子結婚
Import her ass.
帶她入境
Oh, come on, man.
哦，算了，老兄
Dude, what happened to all the honeys
老兄，其他女孩怎麼辦？
we were gonna pimp with your badge, dog?
我們正準備利用你的徽章來吸引她們呢
You're fucking up the plan.
你們會搞砸這個計劃的
I've been thinking, you know?
我在想，你知道嗎？
Love's about sacrifice.
為愛情所犧牲的
Only true measure of it.
只能用事實去衡量
What would you do for Sylvia?
你為西維亞幹了什麼？
Get a job.
找個工作
- Mm... - Nine to fucking five.
- 嗯… - 一個星期干五天
Yeah.
耶
That's love.
這就是愛
Hey.
嘿
Good morning.
早上好
MIKE: So when do you officially
那麼你準備什麼時候正式上任啊？
"Mr. Jim Davis, we regret to inform...
「吉姆·戴維斯先生，我們很遺憾通知您…
I had two beers, right?
我有兩罐啤酒，對嗎？
Yeah.
是的
Going fucking blind or something.
去逍遙一下什麼的
Okay, this letter says, quoting...
好的，這封信上說，引號…
"no longer eligible as a police officer candidate."
不再適合成為一個候選警務人員
What the fuck does that mean?
這是什麼意思？
Come on, dude.
算了，老兄
"No longer eligible"? I mean, what does that sound like?
「不再適合」？我說這個，這是什麼語氣？
They pulled the plug, dude.
他們斷你的路了，老兄
No, no...
不，不…
Why?
為什麼？
Oh, man, I'll bet you...
哦，夥計，我可以和你打賭…
I'll bet you it's 'cause I'm white.
我可以和你打賭就因為我是個白人
I bet it's 'cause you're a dick.
我也可以和你打賭，因為你是個混蛋
No, no, no, Mike, you don't understand.
不，不，不，邁克，你不明白
I am fucked.
我沒戲了
I got to get married.
我正準備結婚
Okay? INS won't let me bring Marta across
知道嗎？移民局不准我帶瑪爾塔入境
unless I got employment.
除非我有工作
I promised her.
我答應她
This fucks up my plan.
這個破壞了我的計劃
This is fucking bullshit, okay?
這是胡說八道，對嗎？
This... these fucking assholes...
這個…這些垃圾…
These fucking assholes!
這些混蛋
What the fuck is their problem, man?!
他們他媽的怎麼回事？！
This is fucking typical cop hate game bullshit!
這些典型的警察作風，胡扯！
Yo, yo, fucking chill, Magilla Gorilla.
冷靜點，大金剛
I mean you're trippir, dude.
我是說你喝多了，老兄
Hey, what the fuck
你他媽的在看什麼？
Fucking dick.
該死的混蛋
Yo, yo,
喲，喲
Jim, Jim...
吉姆，吉姆…
I'm gonna fucking kick your teeth down your puke hole!
我要把打你個滿地找牙！
You fucking want some?
你這個混蛋想要來點什麼是嗎？
Jim, Jim, dude.
吉姆，吉姆，夥計
Kick back, dude.
走開，夥計
The fucking light is green. Get the fuck in the car.
變綠燈了，快上車
Man, fuck. - You're going to catch
你還有機會呢，夥計
What the fuck were you doing?
你看你剛才幹嗎？
Fuck the LAPD, man.
去他的洛杉磯警察局，夥計
What's up with Pasadena, Pomona, Santa Ana and all that?
帕薩迪納市，波莫納，聖安娜和其他地方怎麼樣？
Oh, no, fuck the sticks.
哦，不要，去他的鄉下地方
L.A. City's the shit.
洛杉磯真是個垃圾地方
Hey, Sheriff's Department.
嘿，洛杉磯縣警察局
It's good enough for the INS and still basically L.A., right?
對於移民局來說夠好了吧，而且根本上 來說屬於洛杉磯，對嗎？
Yeah, Sheriff's Department, yeah.
嗯，洛杉磯縣警察局，嗯
They make you work the jails the first two years
他們頭兩年會讓你守監獄
or something.
或者別的
I could be cracking heads
我會給敲破頭
up at the Honor Ranch.
在那個光榮的牧場
I'll give 'em a call, start testing.
我將，嗯，打個電話，去試一下
Yeah.
耶
That's right.
這就對了
Yo, it's just a minor setback, right?
喲，這只是個小挫折，對吧？
Quit trippir, dude.
戒酒吧，老兄
Shit.
靠
Hey, you know what I want to do?
嘿，你知道我想幹嘛嗎？
What?
幹嗎？
I want to get fucked up.
我想站起來
Me, too, man.
我也是阿，夥計
I got to find a job and placate my baby, you know.
我要找個工作來撫慰我的寶貝，你知道的
Sylvia's going to kick your ass?
西維亞逼你了？
Come on, big man, she'll be cool.
來吧，大男人，她會瞭解的
Come on.
來吧
- Bye, Nicole. - Bye.
- 再見，尼科爾 - 再見
Let me get a couple of singles, too, please.
請讓我也買一些散裝的
Sorry, you buy whole pack.
對不起，你要買整包
Be cool, dude.
好了，夥計
If I buy a whole pack
如果我買了一整包
I'm gonna want to smoke it.
我就會想全部抽完
I just want a couple of smokes with my beer.
我只是想喝啤酒的時候來上一兩根
City give me $1,500 ticket.
當局只給我賣1500美金的零售額度
No more.
賣完拉
Asshole.
混蛋
- Thank you, sir.
- 謝謝您，先生
Oh, shit.
哦，去他的
That fucking gangster, man.
夥計，那個真是強盜
Homeboy just ran a six second four-forty.
兄弟剛跑出了一個6秒44
Damn, the chino looked fucking pissed, man.
該死，那個亞洲人看上去很生氣，夥計
You think we'll be able to go back there?
你想我們還能去那裡嗎？
I hate that shit.
我討厭那個混蛋
Fuckir chino lookir at us like we were gonna bust him?
那個混蛋的亞洲人瞪著我們 就像我們想要打他一樣？
Come on, dude. We're wearir suits, man.
沒事，我們衣著整齊，夥計
We totally look like cops.
看上去我們就像個警察
He said he got fined for that shit.
他說他因為這套衣服被罰款
He was just being cautious.
他可是很謹慎呢
Well, we got pisto, we got frajos.
好啦，我們有酒有煙
Only one thing missir.
就差一件事
Be-at-ches.
婊-子
Oh, yeah, I mean besides bitches, man.
哦，耶，我是說婊子之外的，夥計
Yesca? Mm-hmm.
- 大麻？ - 嗯哼
Bingo.
猜對咯
I need to feel some reefer madness.
我想感受一下大麻煙的狂野
You sure you want to score some bud, dude?
夥計，你確定你想來點毒品？
You haven't smoked out since like forever, man.
你永遠不會想吐那口煙出來的，夥計
I said I want to get fucked up, man.
我說過我要站起來，夥計
Fuck this purity bullshit.
去你的純情的胡話
Yeah... fuck purity.
嗯…純情的胡話
Aw, man, look at this zero-head, dog.
哦，夥計，看那個光頭，老兄
Stupid-ass cholo.
笨蛋土著
Look at that.
看那裡
That dude's slangir, dog.
那個夥計是黑道上的，老兄
Want to get a dime?
想搞點便宜貨嗎？
JIM: No, I want it all.
不，我要全部拿過來
Go for the stash, man.
去藏東西的地方，夥計
Whoa, go, go, go.
哦，走，走，走
Hey, hey, yo, yo.
嘿，嘿，喲，喲
That's my shit!
那是我的東西
Fuck.
混蛋
Outstanding.
完美
Out-fucking-standing.
太他媽的完美了
That shit was slick.
他是很聰明
That motherfucker just got schooled.
他可能剛剛上學
Bitch-ass cholo.
混蛋土著
- Check this shit out, huh? - Yeah.
- 檢查一下這個東西 - 耶
Nice motherfucking haul. You see that shit, huh?
漂亮的包裝，你看到了嗎，嗯？
Mm. It's not laced either.
也沒有摻過東西
Smell that shit.
聞一下
We just burned my car.
我們剛把我的車毀了
We go back there, we're gonna get shot.
我們回去那裡，我們快要挨槍子啦
Yeah, no shit.
耶，不行
Man, bust that light.
夥計，把它點上火
Roll that shit up.
捲好它
Yeah, yeah, Cool.
耶，耶，酷
Yo, let's drop off some resumes first.
喲，我們先把那些簡歷丟掉
Then we'll smoke out, dude.
然後我們再去吸一口，老兄
Some resumes.
那些簡歷？
Yeah.
是啊
Ah, man, fresh air.
啊，夥計，新鮮空氣
Look.
看
Oh! They're dropped off, man.
哦，它們被丟掉咯，夥計
You fucking asshole, man.
夥計，你真是個混蛋
I got to get a fucking job, man.
我要去找工作呢，老兄
What's your problem, man?
你有什麼問題，夥計？
What the fuck are you doing, dickhead.
你幹了什麼，老兄
Yo, Mike, first day looking...
喲，邁克，第一天找…
nobody ever gets a job their first day looking.
沒有人會在第一天就找到工作的
Come on, don't sweat it, man.
來吧，不要不安啦，夥計
Hey, I can't fuck around tomorrow.
嘿，我明天不能亂逛了
I got to get a job for sure.
我確定要找份工作
This is your job, man.
這就是你的工作，夥計
So act like a fucking professional,
那就干的專業點
spark up the goods, 'cause we got a lot of work to do.
把它點上火，我們還有很多事情幹呢
It's harsh. It's good, though.
儘管很刺鼻，但這是個好東西
You okay?
你還好嗎？
How are those lungs, baby?
你的肺怎麼樣啊，寶貝？
There it is.
這就是
That magic feeling.
那個神奇的感覺
Damn, look at that bitch.
啊，看那個妓女
Oh, damn.
哦，該死
Fuck, yeah.
干啊，耶
She's fucking good.
她幹起來一定很不錯
I bet she got skills. I want to get laid.
我敢打賭她一定有很多技巧，我想躺下了
You just saw your woman.
你剛去看過你的女人吧
Only hit her once, man.
只搞過一次，老兄
We can't go nowhere alone. They got me sleeping in the car.
我們不能單獨行動 他們讓我睡在車上
Family's got that ass under guard, huh?
他們把她看得很嚴，嗯？
Lock and key.
鎖和鑰匙的遊戲
Fuck, I want to get laid.
討厭，我真得很想躺一下
Pay a visit to my harem, huh?
去我的後宮走走，嗯？
Online, pornmeister.
色情人士上線
Uh-uh, let's go to Letty's pad, man.
嗯-嗯，我們去萊蒂的公寓吧，夥計
How much you want to bet I hit it.
你打賭多少錢我能上她
- She won't, dog. - How much you want to bet?
- 她不會的，老兄 - 你想賭多少？
She won't give you shit, dog.
她不會鳥你的，老兄
You big time fucked her over.
你和她已經幹過了
Aw, man, I popped that poodahey.
啊，夥計，我打開了潘多拉盒子
I got that mind control, man.
我可以控制她的精神，夥計
How much you want to bet I get back up in it?
你想打賭多少錢我和她幹？
20 bucks?
20美金？
You ain't got 20 bucks.
你不會拿到這20美金的
So, neither do you, man.
你也拿不到，夥計
Come on, shake on that shit.
來吧，接受這個賭注
Come on.
來啊
What the fuck, let's go.
這是幹嘛阿，我們走
I got it.
我來了
What's up, Patty?
最近怎麼樣，帕蒂？
- Y tu hermana? - She ain't here.
- 你姐姐呢？ - 她不在這裡
Y sabes que?
你知道嗎？
You're not welcome in this house.
這裡不歡迎你
Sure, Patty.
知道了，帕蒂
I'd love to come in.
我還是喜歡進來
Thank you.
謝謝
Are they here?
他們到了？
You're looking fine, as fuck, chulas.
你看上去很不錯，親愛的
Don't... don't touch me, please.
不要，請不要碰我
Hey, hey.
嘿，嘿
You got to get out of here.
你要離開這裡
Letty...
萊蒂
I just wanted to see you again.
我只是想再看看你
Hey, Patty, you want to grab me a pisto or something?
嘿，帕蒂，你想給我點酒或者別的嗎？
I ain't grabbing you shit.
我什麼都沒有給你
Oh, you still got a mouth, huh?
哦，你還有一張嘴呢，嗯？
Maybe one day you'll learn how to keep it shut.
也許有天你會學會怎麼閉上它
Laters. I'm going to my room.
一會見，我回房間去了
You know you have to run his ass out of here.
你知道你必須把他趕出去
Baby.
寶貝
Let's sit down.
我們坐下說
No, no, no.
不，不，不
So, um...
這樣，嗯…
You a cop yet?
你已經當上警察了？
I'm working on it.
我還在努力
Y tu?
你呢？
Que andas haciendo?
你在做什麼？
Well, you know, I'm going to L.A. Trade Tech.
你知道，我準備去洛杉磯貿易技術大學
It's good you're doing positive shit.
很好啊，你做了正確的選擇
What, after everything I don't get a kiss?
幹嘛，經歷了這麼多事之後 我不能得到一個吻？
It's because of everything you can't get a kiss.
就因為這些事發生之後 你不能夠得到一個吻
Oh, come on, come here.
噢，來吧，來吧
Yeah.
耶
Don't.
不要
Jim, I got a boyfriend.
吉姆，我有男朋友了
Who?
誰？
Flaco.
弗萊克
You're back with that
經歷那麼多事之後還跟著他，萊蒂？
You're not fucking him, are you?
你沒和他上床吧，是嗎？
Please tell me no.
請告訴我沒有
Yes. So... just go.
是的，所以，你走就是啦
'Cause there's nothing here for you, Jim.
這裡沒有你的東西，吉姆
See?
看到沒有？
Okay?
好了嗎？
I don't believe this shit, Letty.
我不信這個，萊蒂
You're too good for that.
那個垃圾配不上你
You gotta go.
你必須走
Go. Please!
請走吧
Let me talk to them.
讓我和他們說
No, Jim, don't be stupid. Please.
不要，吉姆，不要做蠢事，求你了
Okay? Largate. Just go.
好嗎，走吧，離開就好了
I guess it's later days.
我想最近這幾天和他們說
Largate. Just go!
離開，快走
Flaco, the pinchi guero's here!
弗萊克，吉姆在這
Apuarte, Jim! Hurry up!
是吉姆，快點
- Fuck him up! - I got him!
我抓到他就弄死他
Fucking white boy!
該死的小白臉
What's up, faggot?!
想幹什麼，死變態？
We're going to fuck you up!
我們弄死你！
Yo! Pop the trunk
喲，打開後尾箱
so I can handle this shit!
我把這傢伙塞進去
Fuck you, puto!
去你的，混蛋！
I'll bust you!
我打死你！
Leave him alone!
別打他了！
Pop the fucking trunk!
開那個該死的後尾箱
Jim!
吉姆
Oh, you fucked up!
哦，你們完蛋了！
Get your fucking knees down on the curb now!
馬上給我跪在馬路邊上
Get the fuck over there, man!
到這裡來，夥計！
Don't fucking move unless you want your brains hanging out!
不要亂動除非你想你的腦袋開花
What's your problem, Flaco?
有什麼問題嗎，弗萊克？
Motherfucker!
渾蛋！
Fucking knees on the curb, man!
跪到馬路邊上，夥計！
That's right!
這就對了！
Interlock your fingers behind your heads, Flaco!
手指交叉放在腦後，弗萊克！
You deaf fuck!
你聾了？
Yo, Mike.
喲，邁克
Yeah?
耶？
Do up their ride.
檢查一下他們的車
Freeze, bitch!
不要動，雞婆！
I'm going to take that big ass of yours home,
我將把你的屁股從你那裡拿走
hit it for a minute, you know?
然後干它幾分鐘，知道嗎？
Fuck off!
滾開
Now you got it.
現在你知道了
Yo, relax, homie.
喲，放鬆，朋友
You break Letty's heart, I'm coming for your mom.
你傷了萊蒂的心，我也會這樣對你媽的
Fuck!
去你的！
Hey, haina.
嘿，海娜
Whoo!
噢！
Fuck off! Oh, yeah?
- 滾開！ - 哦耶？
What you got down here?
你把什麼放在哪裡？
(whistles): Oh...
噢…
Liking that.
喜歡這樣嗎
Damn! Those are badass kicks, dog.
該死，這些惹事的壞蛋，老兄
Lucky you got little bitch feet,
你很幸運有雙妓女的小腳
else I'd be stomping around in them motherfuckers.
要不我就狂踩上他們幾腳
- Fuck you, puto. - Huh?
- 去你的死變態 - 嗯？
- Yeah. Fuck you. - Yes?
- 嗯，去你的 - 是嗎？
You fucking stay still!
你們繼續在那裡跪著！
Bitches! If you didn't have that fucking gun,
雞婆！如果你們不是有槍的話
ese, it wouldn't be about shit, homie.
事情就不會這樣，夥計
Not fucking shit!
那就沒這樣的事！
Hey, later, Patty!
嘿，再見，帕蒂
I hope you're not pregnant, but you know
我希望你沒有懷孕，但你知道 你想我射到你裡面去
Fuck you!
去你的
Bye, Letty!
再見，萊蒂
Salud.
乾杯
Diwy up the bounty, dude. I know you got some cash.
分錢吧，老兄，我知道你拿到些現金
I know I got more than that.
我知道我拿了些更好的東西
Yeah. Here we go.
耶，我們看看
Shit.
暈
That's my pussy she's giving away there.
他給我的女友用的，她可是送給他了
Homeboy uses extra large.
那個夥計用的是加大號的
Man, that's it? Next time,
夥計，就這些？下一次
jack someone with a job.
要挾他們給份工作算了
Well, fuck you. What did you get, their lunch?
哇，去你的，你拿了什麼？ 他們的午飯？
Check it out.
看一下
Holy shit. You're kidding me.
哇，開玩笑
Whoo! It's a fucking Ruger P-94. Nine millimeter.
噢，這個可是魯格P-94手槍，9毫米口徑
14, plus one in the chamber.
14發，還有1發在槍膛
It's a good fucking gun. Durable.
真是把好槍，很耐用
It's brand-new.
這可是全新的
It's a BB gun.
這個是玩具槍
Yeah. Cool.
是的，很酷
Here you go, dog.
給你，老兄
About time you got a cohete.
是時候你有把槍了
No. I don't want it.
不，我不想要
Why the fuck not? I'll use it.
- 為什麼不？ - 我會亂開槍的
That's a good reason. Sell it.
這是個好理由,賣掉它
How much you think we can get for the gun?
你認為我們可以賣多少？
Two bills, maybe three. Costs six new.
200美元，可能300，新的要600
We'll sell it and split the greenery.
我們賣了它然後分錢
You sure?
確定嗎？
It's cool, dude.
不錯啊，夥計
50-50.
對半分帳
Good BB gun though.
儘管是玩具槍，可是也不錯
Shoot some birds and shit.
可以打鳥和些別的
Hey, put that shit away.
嘿，放好它
Looks real as hell.
看上去可是和真的一樣
Not a bad day's work.
今天工作收穫不錯
Get down to business though.
還是回去幹正經事吧
I know you didn't get any.
我知道你什麼也沒有
So pay up, motherfucker.
還要繳租呢，混蛋
Dick.
混蛋
Hello. This is a message for Michael Alonzo.
你好，這是給邁克爾·阿蘭左的留言
This is Bob Luell at the Palm Glen Group.
這裡是棕櫚峽谷集團
We have reviewed your resume,
我們審查了你的簡歷
and would like to make an appointment
想約您談談
for later in the week.
在這個星期內的隨後幾天找個時間
Please call me at your
請給我電話
earliest convenience.
在你最近方便的時候
Thank you.
謝謝
Huh? That's good.
- 嗯？ - 很好
One more? This is fun.
再來一個？這很好玩
Sounded a little gay, but it was good.
像個小男孩的聲音，不過很不錯
No, no, no. No. That's it, dude. That's it.
不，不，不，夠了，兄弟，夠了
I get too many callbacks,
我收到太多回電
Sylvia's going to get suspicious.
西維亞會起疑心
Oh, Sylvia's going to be kissing your ass.
西維亞會誇你
Not if she recognizes your voice.
如果她認出你的聲音就不會誇我
Oh, she won't. Here, sir.
哦，她不會的，給你，先生
No, no, no, no, no. I'm cool.
不，不，不，不，不，不用啦
- Come on. - I'm cool.
- 來吧 - 不用啦
I want to get home before the little woman and sober up.
我想在我小女人回家之前到家 然後醒一下酒
Come on, bro. One brew.
來吧，夥計，就一瓶
All right, but hey,
好吧，但，嘿
I got to look for a job tomorrow for sure.
我確定明天要去找份工作
Okay? I can't be getting fucked up
知道嗎？我不想背著西維亞
behind Sylvia's back when I'm supposed
把這件事情搞砸，我本來
to be looking for work, man.
要去找工作的，夥計
Not cool. Tomorrow, for sure.
- 不錯 - 明天，肯定會
I got to find a job, too.
我明天也要去找份工作
Hello.
你好
Yes, sir.
是的，先生
Yes, sir. That is correct.
是，先生，完全正確
Six years.
六年
Honorably discharged.
光榮退伍
Yes, sir.
是，先生
I would love to.
我非常樂意
Believe me, I would welcome the opportunity.
相信我，我會珍惜這個機會
Tomorrow
明天完全沒有問題
Thank you, sir. You have a good day, too.
謝謝您，先生，也祝您有愉快的一天
Good-bye, sir.
再見，先生
That was the man, huh? You're all "Sir,
這個就是你想接到電話的人吧 你嘴邊掛著「先生，先生
sir, sir."
先生，先生」
Yes! Fucking yes! Thank God!
是的！是的！感謝上帝！
That was the man! That was the Federal man!
就是他！聯邦官員！
The Federal man!
那個聯邦官員！
Department of Homeland Security
國土安全部
wants me to come in tomorrow to start testing!
希望我明天過去開始測試！
Oh, shit!
哦，不錯！
Fucking A, my brother!
一級棒，我的兄弟！
That shit is righteous, motherfucker!
那裡比較公正點，夥計
It's on, homie!
看我的，夥計！
Wow, man. Tomorrow.
- 哦，兄弟 - 明天
So what the fuck you going to do now, dude?
那麼你現在準備幹嘛，夥計？
I got to take a piss test.
我要去接受尿檢
If I'm cool, I'm in the house.
如果我搞掂，我就進去了
Yeah! Oh!
哦！耶！
Shit, dude, do they piss test for weed?
完了，兄弟，他們會進行 針對大麻的尿檢嗎？
Oh, shit!
噢，糟糕！
You fucked up, man.
你搞砸了，兄弟
Oh, fuck.
哦，糟糕
I fucked up.
我搞砸了
Oh, fuck. I fucked up.
哦，可惡，我搞砸了
Fuck! Oh...
可惡！哦…
You know, one dope molecule, and I'm done.
你知道的，只要發現一個毒品微粒 我就完蛋了
And they will burn me
然後他們會利用
with every law enforcement outfit in the country.
這個國家的法律所賦予的 一切制裁力量來毀掉我
Shit!
糟糕！
Wait, wait, wait, wait, dude.
等等，等等，等等，等等，夥計
Look at me. Look at me.
看著我，看著我，看著我，看著我
Hey, there's a way out of every fucking situation.
嗨，天無絕人之路
- Right? Relax, dude. - Yeah, yeah.
- 對嗎？放鬆，夥計 - 耶，耶
Yeah. I'm going to do what I got to do, you know?
耶，我會幹我該幹的事情的，知道嗎？
It's cool. Fuck, yeah.
不錯，好了，耶
I'll pass that shit.
我會通過尿檢的
Hell, yeah. Yeah.
天啊，耶，耶
Of course you will, dude!
你當然會了，兄弟！
Later, loco.
再見，瘋子
Don't fucking trip, dude.
別犯渾阿，兄弟
All right.
好
(sighs): Shit.
該死
Eat.
吃吧
Come in, dumb ass!
進來，傻瓜！
What's up, dog?
怎麼樣啊，老兄？
What up, dog...
怎麼樣，老兄…
Hey, Jim. Want some coffee?
嘿，吉姆，來點咖啡？
Sure.
好的
Want some eggs? There's extra.
來點雞蛋？那裡還有
Yes, ma'am. Please.
好的，謝謝
I, uh, heard about the LAPD.
我，呃，聽說了洛杉磯警察局的事
Sorry about that.
對此很遺憾
I thought they guaranteed you a job.
我以為他們會給你份工作呢
Yea. Me, too.
嗯，我也是這麼想
Well, maybe it wasrt meant to be.
哦，那也許並不意味著什麼
You know, you being a cop.
你知道，你想當一個警察
Tell her what's up, dude.
告訴她發生了什麼，兄弟
Well, I applied
好的，我向所有的聯邦執法機構
to all the Federal law enforcement agencies.
遞交了申請
You know, ATF, Border Patrol,
你知道，美國酒精煙草與火器管理局 邊境巡邏處
ICE, Homeland Security, all of them.
移民與海關執法局，國土安全部，全部機構
And Homeland Security's interested in me.
現在國土安全部對我有興趣
They want me to come in today and start testing.
他們要我今天過去開始測試
Wow. That's great. How sure is this?
噢，不錯啊，有多大可信度？
Well, I got a urinalysis today.
嗯，今天我要去驗尿
If I pass that, I'll be a Special Agent candidate,
如果過關，我就可以成為一個 專職機構的候選人
and then I could be out of here next month.
然後可能下個月離開這裡
You haven't been smoking out, have you?
你還沒有被查出什麼，是嗎？
Nah. Chilled on that shit a while back.
嗯，冷靜下來就可以過關
Good. Well, thanks for driving Mike around yesterday.
不錯，那麼，謝謝你昨天載邁克兜風
- Yeah, sure. - Yeah, bro.
- 耶，沒問題 - 耶，兄弟
Three callbacks.
3個回電
Damn! Good!
噢！太好了！
We dropped off enough resumes. Whoo!
我們發了夠多的簡歷，喔！
Got more.
還有呢
- Yeah!
- 耶！
Well, you have to keep trying
好的，你要不停的去找
until something happens.
直到找到為止
Finding a job is a job, right?
找工作也是一種工作，對吧！
Lunch money.
給你午飯錢
Thank you.
謝謝
And good luck today.
今天走好運
- Love you. - I love you, too.
- 我愛你 - 我也愛你
Good luck.
好運
And, Jim, good luck on your pee test.
還有，吉姆，祝你尿檢走運
I hope you studied.
我希望你準備好了
I'm going to cram for it.
我為了尿檢在狂吃東西呢
Man, that's freaky.
兄弟，她可是變幻不定
She was in a good mood.
她今天心情不錯
Breakfast and beer money?
午飯錢和啤酒錢？
Yeah, dude.
是的，兄弟
She heard the messages last night.
她昨晚聽到電話留言了
She got me a sixer.
她給我打了六分
I slammed two last night.
我昨晚可是打出2次6分
Out-fuckir-standing!
太完美了
Now we know beer is just a phone call away.
現在我們知道啤酒也 就是一個電話就搞掂了
Yeah.
是的
Yeah. We talked shit out last night, though.
是的，我們昨晚就把這件事 敞開來談
You know? Hey, all she wants is for me to get a job.
你知道嗎？嘿，她所要的就是 我找份工作
I shouldn't be playing her like that.
我不能再這樣戲弄她
Dude, you had a good job,
夥計，你有份好工作
with that, uh, with that Web design shit.
有著，嗯，是個網頁設計的工作
Had, dude. Had.
有的，夥計，是有這麼一個
All right? All that shit's in India now.
對嗎？有關東西現在都在印度
Want a cold one? No, later.
- 想來瓶凍一點的嗎？ - 不，遲點再說
You got any vinegar?
你這裡有醋嗎？
Vinegar? What for?
醋？幹嗎用？
(exhales): Ah...
啊…
(groans): Oh...
噢…
Damn, dude!
該死，夥計！
Ah...
啊…
- Man! - That is fuckir sick, man.
- 夥計！ - 你有病阿，夥計
What'd you do that for?
你這樣干有什麼用？
- Shuts down the old kidneys. - Ooh.
- 讓老腎臟休息一下 - 噢
Come on, let's roll.
來，我們上吧
Grab me that bag, dude.
拿那個袋子過來，夥計
Little trick I learned in the service.
服役時候學會的一點小把戲
Aw, that's sick, dude.
噢，好噁心，夥計
You're gonna stick a turkey baster in your dick?
你想把一個這個滴管放到你的 老二里面去？
Quit looking, faggot.
別看，死變態！
You wish.
如你所願
(groans): Oh, man.
哦，夥計
(yells in pain) Fuckir...
哦
shit, dude.
該死，夥計
Oh, fuckir shit...
啊，該死…
Aw, motherfucker!
噢，混蛋！
That was...
那個樣子…
unpleasant.
很不舒服
(quiet groan): Man...
夥計…
Man, I want to get this shit over with.
夥計，我想快點結束
You know, my teeth are floating.
你知道，我的牙齒在打顫
Oh...
哦…
You get those in the military, dog?
這些是你在軍隊裡面拿的嗎，老兄？
I was a Ranger.
我當過突擊隊員
Your mom still suck a mean dick, hmm?
你媽還能口交，嗯？
Gotcha! Shouldrt ignore people.
抓到你啦！不要忽略別人的存在
Why don't you go fuck yourself!
你為什麼不自己玩去！
Hey!
嘿！
Let's play nice,
我們幹得漂亮點
boys.
小伙子
I have everyone's "Consent to Urinalysis" form signed
我持有你們「同意尿檢」的簽有
and dated, am I right?
名字和日期的表格，我說的沒錯吧？
ALL: Yes, sir.
是的，先生
Good. I'm Agent Richards.
好的，我是理查茲探員
Jackets off.
脫下夾克
I will now administer the easiest test
我現在負責國土安全部
Homeland Security will ever give you,
對你們進行的早期檢查
the whizz quiz.
這是個專業測試
Roll up both sleeves past the elbow.
把雙手的衣袖捲過手肘
Remove all gloves, rings, watches, bracelets,
除下所有手套，戒子，手錶，手鐲
jewelry, Band-Aids and bandages.
珠寶，急救繃條，繃帶
I want to see nothing but bare hands and forearms.
我只想看空空的雙手和前臂
Wiggle your fingers.
抖一下你們的手指
Let me see both sides.
讓我兩邊都看到
Beautifully done.
幹得漂亮
Again, gentlemen, no talking.
再說一次，先生們，不准說話
Detweiler, is it?
是德特維勒嗎？
You're with me.
你跟我來
(whispers): Fucker.
混蛋
RICHARDS: Next!
下一個
Name?
名字？
Davis, Jim.
戴維斯·吉姆
Ah, the Ranger.
啊，突擊隊員
Yes, sir.
是，先生
- You serve? - 101st.
- 在那裡服役？ - 第101部隊
- High speed. - All right.
- 快點好嗎 - 好的
Think you can fill that, son?
你可以裝滿這個嗎，孩子？
I could fill a goddamn trash can, sir.
我可以加滿一個垃圾桶，先生
(laughs): You're full of piss and vinegar, aren't you, Jim?
你一肚子的尿和醋，對嗎，吉姆？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生
Hey, unload that shit before you clown with it, okay?
嘿，你裝神扮鬼之前卸下子彈，好嗎？
I don't want my head blown off
我可不想在事情都妥了時候
just when I'm getting it straight.
腦袋開花
Pop! What's it like
崩！這會是怎麼樣
to just straight-up whack a motherfucker?
當直接攻擊一個混蛋的時候？
What's it like? I mean, what the fuck, you know?
怎麼樣？我是說，那個，你知道？
It's like nothing. What's it supposed to be like?
那個什麼都不是，那個應該是什麼樣？
You tell me.
你來告訴我
You were busting heads for the military.
你可是曾經為軍隊爆別人的頭
I can't talk about this shit, Mike.
我不能說這種事，邁克
But I will tell you one thing... you point and shoot,
但我可以跟你說件事… 你瞄準然後射擊
pop, pop, move on, fuck 'em, they shouldn't have been there,
砰，砰，砰，繼續前進，就會發現 他們不在原地了
you move the fuck on.
你要前進
You do not stop and think about it.
你不能停下或者想這事
- It's not a big deal. - So if it's nothing,
這不是什麼了不起的，所以 這個什麼都不是
then what you getting all mad for?
那麼你為什麼生氣？
I'm not getting mad.
我沒有生氣
I just hate stupid questions, Mike.
我只是討厭愚蠢的問題，邁克
You think you killed a lot of Commies?
你認為你殺了很多共產黨員？
- They werert Commies, dumb ass. - Then what were they?
- 他們不是共產黨員，混蛋 - 那麼他們是什麼人？
You know what they were... they were fuckir Hajjis,
你知道他們是… 他們是該死的穆斯林
terrorists, the bad guys.
恐怖分子，壞蛋
Did you like it? (quietly): Oh, shit.
- 你喜歡嗎？ - 噢，不
Did you dig it?
想通了嗎？
You bust a nut? (popping sound)
你感覺像射精？
Not fuckir now, man. Seriously.
別鬧了，夥計，認真點
You're killing my buzz, dude.
你把我搞頭暈了，老兄
Aw, kick back, stress case.
交房租，那才是重點
Are we on a mission to sell this piece or what?
我們還有賣槍的任務呢！
Hell, yeah.
當然
Let's sell this fuckir piece.
讓我們把這該死的槍賣了
Got to get some scratch, you know what I'm saying?
去搞點現鈔，懂麼？
Yo, Darrel!
達羅爾
- Yo, yo, yo, Darrel! - Wake the fuck up, Darrel!
- 喲，喲，喲，達羅爾！ - 媽的起床啦，達羅爾！
Darrel!
達羅爾！
Come on, come on, come on, wake up and fuckir
快起床啊∼
shine!
該死的太陽都曬到屁股了
Y'all need to knock this shit off right now.
急毛，我正要來開門
- (Mike chuckling) - Hey, what's up, bro?
什麼風把你們吹來了？
Come on in, motherfuckers.
進來吧
Get your little ass up in here.
小屁股抬起來
Shit!
我靠
Oh, man...
夥計…
y'all scared the fuck out of me, man.
你們嚇我一跳
You motherfuckers got ties on.
你個混球領帶都打起來了
I saw that city-lookir car pull up...
我看到那巡邏車停下來
I thought y'all was some rollers or shit.
我以為是因為一些滑旱冰的人
I just got out of County.
我正打算出郡
- $9,600. - No shit. When?
- 罰了我9600美圓 - 他媽的，什麼時候的事？
Yesterday.
昨天
MIKE: Damn. What'd they put on you?
該死的，他們怎麼能這樣對你？
Some bullshit.
儘是胡扯
I saw some wrong-ass shit
他們這群蠢貨
up in there, dude.
這管管那管管
I ain't ever going back to that motherfucker.
我再也不隨便出郡了
It scared you straight, huh?
這事對你打擊挺大
- Mm-hmm. - Hey, you get booty-played?
嘿，你有什麼新玩意？
Hell, no.
我去哪裡弄來？
You over there tickling your brown eye, dog?
別對我擠眉弄眼，老兄
They-they put some jelly on there, serve some syrup?
他們在那放點果子凍，再搾點果汁
- You toss the salad? - Hey, you know, nigga,
- 最好拌點沙拉 - 嘿，你知道的
I kept my ass to the wall and my mouth shut.
我一邊站著，不支聲行不？
Shoot.
媽的
I almost lost my job over that shit.
我差點因為這蠢事砸了飯碗
Fuckir around in there.
簡直是陰魂不散
Oh, God...
啊，我的天那…
- You a cop? - Nope.
- 你是條子？ - 不是
Rejected his ass.
他吃了閉門羹
Fuck you.
我靠
I'm getting in the Feds' car.
我上了聯邦調查局這「賊船」
(laughs): Damn...
「天哪」
That's what I'm talking about!
那正是我要說的
Ah, you hear that?
你聽到了麼？
This motherfucker gonna be a Fed.
這鳥人居然要當個聯邦探員了
You been wanting that shit, too.
你也不在是個小混混了哈
It's my dream, dude.
那工作正是我夢寐以求的，老兄
So, you gonna do that shit right,
所以，要不好好做吧
or, you know, you gonna do a little shit on the side?
要不就搗搗糨糊
I'm gonna get my own thing going.
我有自己的一套做法
You know, I'll be flipping shit, make a little money.
我真他媽高興，可以賺點小錢了
- You know? - (laughing)
你明白？
This motherfucker gonna have shit wired.
這鳥人居然上崗了
Scary, huh?
怕怕…
Check this shit out.
瞧瞧這玩意
This is sweet!
小寶貝
We jacked some eses. Got a BB gun, too.
我們洗劫了些小混混， 還弄了把「ＢＢ彈玩具槍」
- A BB gun? - Yo.
「ＢＢ彈玩具槍」
Goddamn!
該死的
This is a nice little machine.
這真是個可愛的小「玩具」
Three bills, it's yours.
三張大鈔，拿去
I ain't got three bills, dog.
我身無分文了，老兄
My lawyer cleaned me out.
我的律師「洗劫了」我
(sighs): Man...
兄弟
I ain't got no ways or means, homie.
實在是沒辦法，兄弟
I need this shit, too.
我真很想要這寶貝
Bring the heat to these motherfuckers
給巡邏的傢伙點顏色看看
We need ends, dog.
親兄弟明算帳，老兄
Who'll give us three bills for it?
大鈔我們找誰拿去？
Hey, uh, I know a cat.
嘿，我知道塊「肥肉」
Hangs out at, uh... La Licha
在理查混的
on, uh, Santa Fe.
去聖達菲
Yeah, I know that place. He cool?
對，我認識那，他很酷？
Oh, man, he's old school, real cool.
恩，夥計，守舊派一個，真的酷
Veterano named Eddie.
叫艾迪的老傢伙
He there today?
他今天在那麼？
Oh, that's just like his living room, dog.
那就像他的家一樣，老兄
Yeah. Yeah, I'll hook you up. Don't worry about it.
別擔心，我罩著你們
Cool, cool.
可以的
Y'all need to come up, dog.
我們這就動身去，老兄
Can you do me a favor?
能幫我個小忙麼？
Sure.
沒問題
You mind calling my pad
掛個電話去我家
and leaving a fake message
留個言
so my old lady thinks I'm out there looking for a job?
那麼我老婆會以為我是出來找工作了
Instead you out getting fucked up.
而不是你來我這胡鬧
Can you hook me up,
幫個忙吧
or what, dog? Huh?
怎麼樣，老兄？
Yeah? All right.
沒問題
Check this out.
仔細看下這個
Uh, just call, right? (coughs)
打個電話就行
And say you're from that place right there
然後說你是那工作人員
and that you want to schedule an interview, dude.
安排我來面試，老兄
Man, y'all some devious motherfuckers, man.
夥計，你真會動歪腦筋
Hey, hey, make sure she can't star-69 my shit.
嘿，確保她不在家
Nah, she's... Serious, man.
- 沒事，她是… - 嚴肅點，夥計
I ain't trying to break up no shit on this.
我不想把事辦砸了
All right, it's ringing. Here you go.
好了，電話通了，靠你了
- Be serious, dude. - Hey, hey,
- 嚴肅點，老兄 - 嘿，嘿
don't sound like a fag, either, man.
別用你的民工腔調說，夥計
That's how he be sounding.
那是他的風格
Uh, Mr. Alonzo,
阿蘭佐先生
I'm calling from Sunouse Properties,
我是「太陽地產」公司的
uh, to schedule an interview.
希望你約個時間來面試
Uh, please call me back at 213-555-
回電請至213- 555-
15-15.
15- 15
damn, dog!
該死，老兄
That shit was good, dude!
演得真像，老兄
Damn, they should give you a fuckir Oscar for that shit.
應該給你頒個奧斯卡獎
That shit was cold, man.
這笑話真冷
- Playing your woman like that. - Aw, come on, man.
- 和你老婆說去吧 - 啊，來吧，夥計
I did three yesterday... she bought him a six-pack.
我昨天打了3次，她給他買了啤酒
What's one call get you, a fuckir 40
一個電話給你什麼好處？40盎司的好酒？
I'll be like this. Look.
我會像這樣，瞧
- (all laughing) - You know you would!
你就這副腔調
Bitch-ass motherfucker.
媽的真搞笑
This is good shit, right?
好玩吧，夥計？
I told you it was some good shit, dog.
我在給你拌幾個更好玩的，老兄
Hey, we got to bounce.
我們得動身了
Oh, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不
No, no, y'all just got here, dog.
不，不，你們屁股都還沒坐熱呢，老兄
Can't happen.
別這樣
- Come on. - Yo, uh, tell that guy Eddie
- 走吧 - 告訴那叫艾迪的傢伙
that we're gonna cruise through there a little later.
我們晚一點過去
Okay?
行麼？
- Aw, yeah. - Later, man.
再見，兄弟
I wish I had the money.
我希望能拿到錢
That's a sweet-ass piece, though.
那傢伙是塊肥肉
That shit'll keep the porch clean.
那傢伙不會惹事
Motherfuckers like y'all won't be banging on my shit.
像你們這樣，他肯定買帳
Hey, Jim.
嘿，吉姆
We should lose the monkey suits, dude.
把這身傻衣服脫了，老兄
Quien es?
這是誰啊？
Hey, bring us, dos pistos, por favor,
嘿，給我們上點好酒好菜
mi reina.
我的皇后
Damn.
該死的
Hey, dog, I don't think they like us here.
老兄，看樣子我們不太受歡迎
Fuck 'em.
去他們的
I got my shit.
我他媽的
They make a move, I'm blasting.
讓他們去，我們狂歡
Which one of these fools is Eddy?
哪個蠢蛋是艾迪?
Yeah. I don't know.
我不清楚
They're all paisas here.
這都是些印度人
Hey, why don't you ask that homegirl right there?
幹嘛不問下那個萬事通小妞？
Sientate, guapa.
很性感啊
Mm.
嗯
Habla Espanol?
會講西班牙語？
Si.
是的
Que bien.
很好啊
Sabas donde esta el Eddy?
艾迪在哪？
Eddy, te hablan.
艾迪，他們找你
Que paso?
什麼事？
Do I know you?
我認識你們嗎？
My homeboy Darrell said to talk to you.
我朋友達羅爾叫我和你談談
Darrell? Yeah.
- 達羅爾？ - 對
I'm Jim, homie.
叫我吉姆，夥計
What's up, man? Mike, dog.
怎麼了夥計？我叫麥克
All right. So what's up?
好吧，有何貴幹？
Need a cohete?
要槍嗎？
Maybe.
或許
What kind?
型號？
Ruger P-94, brand-new.
魯格P-94，全新
Ruger, huh? Yeah.
- 魯格，恩？ - 對
How many mags?
多少發子彈？
One high cap. I'll throw in the hollow points.
高容量，我會加鉛彈的
Strictly Black Talons, homes.
絕對是銀爪彈
Homies be wearing vests these days,
小流氓最近都開始穿防彈衣了
know what I'm saying?
懂麼？
Is it new?
是新貨麼？
Yeah, it's brand-new.
當然，全新
Where's it at?
貨在哪？
I can get it.
我身上
How much?
多少錢？
Three bills.
三張大鈔
I'll give you $250 if it's new.
新貨，我給你250
If not, I'll give you $200.
不然，給你200
Cool.
爽氣
You got the feria, homie?
花錢圖個平安，夥計
I can get it.
我要了
Orale.
好
Let's kick back, have a couple pistos
放鬆下，來兩杯酒
before we handle business, eh?
然後一手交錢一手交貨
Hey, guero, you like her?
嘿，兄弟，你喜歡她？
I do need to get laid.
這麼勾著很舒服
There it is right there, brother.
隨便你吧，兄弟
Yo, give me that cohete.
把那槍給我
Mataste a un flor.
你殺死了個女人
Oh, shit!
該死的
Open the fucking door!
快開門！
MIKE: Holy shit, dude!
天那，老兄！
You think he's gonna fuckir die?!
他就這樣掛了？
Sure. Got his carotid.
當然，頸動脈都被割了
Fucker was garden-hosing.
媽的和橡皮管一樣
He'll bleed out.
他失血過多的會
Oh, shit, dude,
該死，老兄
I've seen dudes get shot, man, but I never seen
老兄，我見過挨槍子的 但沒見過那麼殘忍的…
no motherfucking shit like that before, man!
那麼慘的死法誰會見過？
Fucked his shit up, you know?
真他媽的夠狠！
Quick as shit, too. That crack-crack!
下手也利落！就那麼卡- 卡∼
Turned that vato into a fountain of blood.
那傢伙就血流成河了
Why the fuck did he do that, man?
他怎麼那麼殘忍？
That shit could have been over anything, you know?
可能是因為什麼事，要做個了斷吧？
Money, drugs, bitches, respect, whatever.
錢，毒品，女人，自尊等等
That homie, straight-up pimp.
那傢伙也許是個皮條客吧？
You know, maybe he turned out that dude's daughter.
可能是嫖了人家的女兒
Looney tunes and shit,
那人真是瘋了
glass all stuck in his fuckir neck.
玻璃就這麼一下子就戳進了他脖子
Did you see all that fuckir blood over there?!
見過那麼血腥的場面麼？
Yeah, man, the human body's got a gallon.
恩，夥計，人身體裡有一加侖的血呢
Damn!
該死！
I coulda boned Gracie.
我本可以泡上格雷西
She had that proper thickness.
她身材很棒
Look at me, dog.
看著我，老兄
Look at me.
看著我
I'm fuckir traumatized and shit.
我幼小的心靈受傷害了
Yo, homie, that shit don't fuckir faze you at all?
那該死的事對你一點也沒影響？
Oh, man, I seen way worse.
我總是從壞的方面看
Trashcanistan.
特西·肯斯坦
My battle buddy, he got his legs and arms blown off
我的一個戰友
by a booby-trapped motorcycle.
被輛戰車碾下胳膊和腿
Medic saved his ass and he lived.
僥倖生還
He didn't want to, but he did.
殘酷的現實，他無從選擇
I got to face my woman.
我還要去見我女人
How in the fuck am I supposed to play this shit off, huh?
怎麼才能把這該死的事忘記？
Man, you'll do it, player.
夥計，相信你做的到
Hey, baby girl, you cooking?
寶貝，你在烹飪？
Yeah. Where have you been?
你哪去了？
Oh, Jim's pad.
吉姆的公寓
You been drinking?
喝過酒了？
Oh, you know, I had a few brews.
我只喝了一點
A few? Yeah.
- 一點點？ - 當然
You look wasted.
你看起來很疲憊
Don't trip, girl.
乖，寶貝
I've been working all day.
我忙了一整天了
I've been looking for work all day.
找了一天工作
I wish I could hang out and get wasted like the old days.
我想我可以辭職了，像以前那樣過休閒日子
You know what?
你知道麼？
When I'm working, you can lounge.
我工作了，你就等著享福吧
I'll fix this place up,
把這裡裝修下
get you nice clothes and stuff...
給你弄些漂亮衣服和首飾
Mike, Mike, Mike.
麥克， 麥克，麥克
It doesn't have anything to do with money.
這些和錢無關
Come here.
過來這
Sit down. I want to talk to you.
坐下，我有話和你談
Hey, it's not about stuff.
不談錢
It's about you and me needing an equal partner.
談談夫妻間的平等問題
Right.
好
Hey, I know that you supported me through college
感謝你供我上大學
and I'm gonna always
我總是覺得
- owe you for that. - Right.
欠你很多
Now everything's flipped
但現在形勢不同了
and I feel like I'm doing everything alone.
我能獨立生活了
You know, sometimes I feel like you're my kid.
有時我覺得你就像個孩子
I mean, you sneak around like one.
我的意思是你整天游手好閒像個混混
Look... Wow, dude.
瞧，老兄
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Be cool, baby girl,
冷靜點，寶貝
I'm on a mission to get my shit together.
我努力著改變這一切
I applied at this commercial realty company in Studio City,
我已經像一家房產公司投了簡歷
and this black guy, he was the office manager
就是那個黑人，他是部門經理
and he's fuckir hella cool,
他真他嗎酷
you know? We're talkir and all that shit.
我們說了白說
You know? We're just kickir it and all that.
讓這事滾一邊去吧
Did you, did you check the messages?
你檢查電話留言了麼？
Four messages.
四條留言
DARRELL: Mr. Alonzo, I'm calling
阿蘭佐先生，我是「陽光地產」公司的
from Sunouse Properties to schedule an interview.
希望你約個時間來面試
Honey, this is great!
親愛的，太棒了
You better call him first thing in the morning.
你明天早上第一件事就是給他回個電話
MIKE: Oh, damn, dog, that shit was good, dude.
該死，老兄 演得真像，老兄
Damn, they should give you a fuckir Oscar for that shit.
應該給你頒個奧斯卡獎
You just stood there
你給我站住
and you fed me a line of bullshit like it was nothing.
你耍得我團團轉
You should be the lawyer.
你本來可以當個律師
How could you just do that?
你怎麼可以那麼過分？
How could you look me in the eye and lie to me like that?
你怎麼可以注視著我，輕描淡寫地撒謊
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'd rather you hit me.
你真得傷害了我
I'm your clown.
我像個小丑
I'm your fucking clown.
我他媽的像個小丑
And you and Jim are laughing at me?
你和吉姆肯定在嘲笑我！
No, it's not...
不，不是的…
No, no, no, you are so utterly, irrevocably busted!
不，不，不，你真是太失敗了
Why don't you just go play with your little butt buddy?
你怎麼不和你酒肉朋友玩去？
Go cook up more lies.
多撒點謊去
You know, I bet you're doing lines again.
你知道麼，我打賭你還會撒謊
Dude, how could you say that shit?
老兄，你怎麼能那麼說？
I'm not fuckir doing lines again.
我不會再撒謊了
Yeah, right, right.
好，好
I'm not fuckir doing lines again!
我真的不再撒謊了
Right now your word is less than shit.
你現在的承諾一文不值
Maybe you should go.
或許你可以出去了
Just fuckir go.
給我出去
Just fuckir... just go, right?
出去，可以！
Fuck it. I'll fuckir go!
他媽的，我走！
Please, go. Go!
隨便你，走啊！
Then go, Mike!
那麼就快走，麥克！
I'm serious! I'll fuckir go
我是認真的，我走！
except I won't fuckir come back!
永遠不回來
You want me to fuckir go?!
你媽的要我走？
Fuckir go, Mike!
走啊，麥克！
I'll fuckir go then!
走就走！
Get the fuck outta here!
滾出去！
Hello?
喂？
Speaking.
請說
Of course, sir. Absolutely.
當然，先生，完全可以
Thank you very much, Agent Richards.
非常感謝，理查茲特工
Thank you, sir.
謝謝您
Who was that?
誰打來的？
That was the feds, my friend.
聯邦調查局的朋友
I've been informed that I passed my urinalysis
我被告知過了尿檢
and they would like me to go in this morning
他們要我早上過去
to start formal testing.
做正式測驗
Fuck yeah, dude.
真不錯，老兄
I'll be there all day,
我要去一整天
so take my ride, get your ass a job.
你用我的車，去找個工作吧
Let's go.
動起來
Come on. Get your parasitic ass in gear.
來吧，把你生蛌瑣鷑僎}動起來
I had some twisted-ass dreams about that dude being killed.
我做了個荒誕的夢，夢中你被殺了
I slept like a baby.
我睡覺時像個嬰兒
I heard screaming.
我聽到了慘叫
What kind of tests?
什麼類型的測試？
Psychological tests.
心理測試
Geez, you're a freakir psycho, dude.
天那，你就是個小變態
Don't answer that shit honestly.
別裝得太誠實
Hell no.
當然不會
They use the Minnesota Multiphasic Inventory.
他們用明尼蘇達產的測謊儀
It's like 600 questions, cross-referenced
需要問600個問題做參照
to detect deception.
來測慌
They ask the same shit
問題都很像
six different ways. It's lame.
六個方面的，都是廢話
You'll ace it.
你會拿個高分的
Dude, I'm gonna pull it off.
老兄，我會努力的
All I needed was a shot.
我只需要一顆子彈
Gotta play the system.
輕鬆應對測試
Like a piano.
就像彈鋼琴
You done with that crap, son?
準備好上了麼，孩子？
Yes, sir.
是
Let's grab some coffee while these guys finish up.
在他們準備好前，我們弄點咖啡
Bring that with you.
帶上那個
(whispers): I see dumb people.
你個啞巴
We reviewed your LAPD package.
我們看了你在洛杉磯警局做的體檢
Since they ran your background, physical and psych,
身體素質和心理素質上的
we're going with their paper.
我們以他們的作參照
- Navy sucks. - Army swallows.
- 海軍真討厭 - 陸軍真麻煩
Took a little work to pry your jacket loose
脫了外套做些準備活動
from their people.
瞧那些人
They don't much like us poaching from their applicant pool.
他們不像我們那麼招聘
Move it, dirt bag.
別偷懶
Why'd they drop me?
洛杉磯警局為什麼拒我？
Someone here make a call?
這裡有人打小報告？
Nope.
不是
They dropped you on psych, Jim.
你心理測試不通過，吉姆
You blew their profiles.
你不適合那個工作
We're all a little goofy here.
我們這都有點傻
You'd rather be with us, wouldn't you?
你還願意和我們一起，是麼？
Absolutely, sir.
當然，先生
Good answer.
答得好
Have a seat.
過來坐
Said you were bilingual on your app.
簡歷上說你會雙語
They want to test your Spanish.
他們要測試你的西班牙語
We can get that going if you got time.
如果你有時間，我們現在就測
Yes. Sure.
當然有
Who's "they"?
他們是誰？
Your fans upstairs.
你的粉絲，樓上的
Fans upstairs? Who?
樓上的粉絲？誰？
This is some shit above my pay grade,
一群比我工資高的混蛋
but some very important people have an eye on you, Jim.
但是一些要人很重視你
Okay, Mike...
好了，麥克…
Alonzo?
阿蘭佐？
Oh, shit. Joe?!
喔，天那， 喬？！
Damn... What's up, dog?
該死的… 兄弟，你怎麼了？
- Mikey, look at you. - What are you doing here, dude?
- 麥克，瞧你 - 你怎麼在這，老兄?
Mikey, man, check you out.
麥克，夥計，瞧瞧你
What the fuck you doing here?
你他媽的在這做啥？
Fucking grew up. I work here.
媽的升職了，我在這工作
- Get out of here. - Yeah.
- 咱們去逛逛 - 好啊
Dude, you got to come on up.
老兄，你得給我上來
Yeah, I'll show you the office.
呀，給你展示下我的辦公室
Fuck, you're gonna trip, man,
夥計，我帶你兜一圈
I can see the ocean and everything.
景色不錯，還能看到大海
Check you out, fucking ocean view and all that.
瞧瞧你，媽的還有海景
You're wearing a suit now.
你現在人模人樣了哈
- Got your hair cut. - Hey, watch out, baby.
- 理了個頭 - 嘿，寶貝，有型吧
Yeah. Tag no more, huh?
呀，不再梳包頭了哈？
No, man.
不了，夥計
Dude, what's up with your brother, Pedro?
老兄，你兄弟境況如何，佩德羅？
Oh, man, he's in Iraq. He's in a forward unit.
夥計，他在伊拉克，屬於前線部隊
Get the fuck out of here. Yeah.
可以滾了
(muttering): Fuckir Mexicans.
該死的墨西哥人
Bye, sweetie.
再見，小丑
Thank you, sir. I need me some of this, man.
謝謝，先生 我需要這些，夥計
I've been taking piss all day.
我已經尿了一天了
Dude!
老兄！
What?
什麼？
You're not going to
你不會相信的
- I had an interview today. - Yeah?
- 我今天去面試了 - 是麼？
- Remember Crazy Joe? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 記得瘋狂的喬? - 對，對，當然
Dude stomped that guy's face in at Taco Land
老兄把那傢伙臉踩成了墨西哥玉米卷
for grabbing his chick's ass.
因為他摸了他馬子的屁股
Homeboy got his shit together, man.
他狗屎運
Went to UCLA.
去了洛杉磯加利福尼亞大學
Works at this office up in Century City.
在這座奢華的都市裡坐辦公室
I got the hookup, dog.
所以我拿到份工作，老兄
- 12 an hour. - Hoo-hoo!
- 12美圓一小時 - 嗚呼
- That's a lot of lettuce. - That's right.
- 財源滾滾啊 - 是啊
And in three months, I get benefits.
而且在3個月裡我還能拿到津貼
Damn! Benefits?
該死的，還有津貼！
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Shit!
- 耶，耶，耶，耶 - 媽的！
Yeah!
耶！
It's not for sure yet, though, dude.
儘管還不是很確定，老兄
I still got to meet the owner, right.
我還是要去見老闆的
But he says I'm straight.
但是他說我很人直率
It's all good, you know.
其他也都不錯，你知道
You're in. Dude...
你上崗了 老兄…
I'm in. Oh, shit.
- 我上崗了 - 嘔，狗屎
Yeah... What happened?
- 耶… - 你那邊雜樣了？
They want my ass, man. Going back tomorrow
他們媽的要我明天再去次
for a polygraph test.
做個測慌器測試
If I pass that, they'll send me to Georgia next week.
如果我通過了，他們下周就送我去喬治亞州工作
Oh... Damn! It's like that?!
啊哈…天那 真是那樣？！
What's up, lawman?
感覺怎麼樣，警官？
Whoo-hoo!
喔- 喉
How you gonna pass a lie detector test,
你要怎麼通過謊言測試
- you lying motherfucker? - Aw, easy, man.
- 你媽的盡扯淡 - 啊，簡單，夥計
After every question, you just fucking squeeze
每個問題以後，你只要用力擠，
like you're taking a dump, you know, man.
就像在拉屎一樣，懂麼，夥計
- It throws the machine off. Ooh! - Oh, dog.
- 讓機器滾蛋 - 嘔，老兄
You're gonna shit your pants like that, bro.
你那樣的話會拉一身的屎，
Fuck, I think I just did.
媽的，我會那麼幹的
All right, Jim,
當然，吉姆
I'm going to ask you some control questions
我將問你一些控制問題
before we get to the good stuff.
在我們切入正題前
They can be answered just "yes" or "no."
你只需回答「是」或「不是」
Just relax and respond naturally.
放鬆然後自然地回答
Are you ready?
你準備好了麼？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生
You can just answer "yes" or "no."
你只需回答「是」或「不是」
"Is your name Jim Luther Davis?"
「你的名字叫吉姆·盧瑟·戴維斯」
Yes.
是
"Do you live in Los Angeles?"
「你住在洛杉磯？」
"Are you 26 years old?"
「現年26歲？」
Yes.
是
"Are you married?"
「已婚？」
No.
不是
"Are you wearing shoes?"
「你穿鞋了麼」
Yes.
是
"Have you ever smoked marijuana?"
「你吸過大麻？」
"Aside from the occasion you mentioned in your application?"
「離開你申請表中提到的地方？」
No.
不是
Jim, knock it off.
吉姆，別這樣
What, sir?
怎麼了，先生？
Son, I've been doing polygraph examinations
孩子，我做謊言測試的時候
since you were swimming in your daddy's balls.
你還在你爸爸的睪丸裡游泳呢
So I know all the tricks.
所以別和我刷把戲
You've either got a tack in your shoe
你不是在鞋子裡藏了釘子
or you're clinching your butt.
就是把它釘在了你屁股上
I've got spikes all over this thing.
把釘子給我，這事到此為止
If you do it again,
你再敢那麼做
I'm going to void this test
那麼這個測試就算無效
and report that you were uncooperative.
然後你將被報告違紀
Do you understand?
聽明白嗎？
Yes, sir.
是，先生
Walk with me.
跟我走
We've got a problem, Jim.
我們有個問題，吉姆
With what?
因為什麼？
With your candor.
因為你的「坦率」
Come in.
請進
He's here, sir.
他來了
Bring him in.
帶他進來
Jim, this is Mr. Hollenbeck, our regional director.
吉姆，這位是霍倫貝克先生 我們的地方首長
Pleased to meet you, sir.
很高興見到您
Have a seat.
坐吧
Mr. Gillespie.
吉萊斯皮先生
Pleased to meet you, sir.
很高興見到您
Jim, uh...
吉姆，嗯…
you're an exemplary candidate
你是我們考慮的
with valuable operational experience.
有著寶貴實踐經驗的候選人
You've cleared the psych and physical hurdles.
你已經克服了心理和生理上的障礙
Your credit's good, you've kept your nose clean,
你的信用不錯，嗅覺敏銳
you've got the Spanish.
還會說西班牙語
You clearance is still valid.
你的證書依然有效
Everybody we talked to for background
每個和我們談起你背景的人
had only great things to say about you.
都對你有很高的評價
And then you scored a negative-five on the polygraph.
但是你的謊言測試得了負5分
That's indicative of deception.
那意味著欺騙
We were wondering why
我們很不解
until we got the results of urinalysis.
直到拿到了你的尿檢報告才明白
We detected THC metabolites in the urine, Jim.
你的尿裡我們檢測到了大麻代謝物，吉姆
Levels were just below the positive threshold,
濃度相當高，吉姆
but there was a presence.
這是事實
Do you have a drug problem, Mr. Davis?
你有吸毒問題麼？戴維斯先生？
I don't have a drug problem, sir.
我沒有吸毒，先生
I made a very stupid mistake.
我犯了個很愚蠢的錯誤
Would you care to tell us the circumstances
你能解釋下這個情況麼？
of your stupid mistake?
關於你的愚蠢錯誤
I was at a party...
我參加了一個派對
and someone offered me a joint.
然後有人給了我支大麻捲煙
I was pretty angry about not getting into
我當時正為沒能進「洛杉磯格警局」生氣
the LAPD, so I was feeling rebellious and, uh...
所以我感到很難受，然後就…
...I inaled.
吸食了
Someone considering a career in law enforcement
人們認為一個從事執法的人
would be well advised to exercise
需要遵守
a little more discipline.
更多的道德準則
Yes, sir.
是的，先生
I'm on the fence, Doug.
我保持中立，道格
It's your call.
輪到你了
Mr. Davis, I'm in charge of several programs.
戴維斯先生，我負責很多項目
Yes, sir?
是麼？
Had a nice chat with your old commanding officer.
與你的舊上司有過一次「愉快」的對話
Good.
不錯
Recognize these guys?
認識這些傢伙麼？
Huh? Yeah,
恩？是的
they're your buddies.
他們是你的「密友」（俘虜）
Your old Hajji buddies.
你過去在麥加的「密友」（俘虜）
You should work in a deli how you sliced these guys up.
你怎麼把他們切成一片片的 你應該去賣肉
RICHARDS: Jesus Christ.
天那
Oh, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Did I ruin your lunch?
影響到你的食慾了？
You went through those sons of bitches
你審判這些混蛋
like butter.
就像個屠夫
I took my objective
我捕獲我的目標
and did what was necessary
然後做我該做的
to obtain information vital to national security
去獲得對國家安全重要的信息
that saved American lives.
那樣才能救美國人的命
Whacked them all, huh, Jim?
把他們都殺了，吉姆？
My C.O. Told me not to leave anything breathing.
我的長官告訴我不能留活口
- I do what I'm told. - Relax, son.
- 我按命令行事 - 放鬆，孩子
You were getting paid to fuck people up.
我們發你工資讓你發揮特長
You know we're beefing up our anti-narcotics programs
我們正從反毒行動中受益
in Latin America.
在拉丁美洲
Yes, sir.
是的，先生
I had heard some things on the grapevine.
我從謠傳中略之一二
I want you on my team.
我的隊伍需要你
I need someone who can get things done
我需要能幹實事的人
on my task force in Colombia.
我的哥倫比亞特遣部隊
Sir...
先生…
I listed Los Angeles and San Diego on my dream sheet.
我申請表上寫的是洛杉磯或聖地亞哥
No slots in southern California?
沒填南加洲吧？
No, Jim.
沒有，吉姆
I got Colombia.
只有哥倫比亞
That's what I have for you.
那是我為你準備的
If it's not what you want,
如果不想去
thank you for your time.
那麼謝謝你的寶貴時間
You can hit the door.
你可以走人了
What exactly would I be doing?
確切的要我幹些什麼？
Running and gunning in the jungle?
在叢林中奔跑打獵？
Mr. Davis, this is the deal.
戴維斯先生，合同是這樣的
You'll be riding shotgun with the locals
你將要拿著散彈鎗
as interpreter-advisor on sharp end operations.
作為一個情報人員完成軍事任務
You'll be in some very hot areas.
或者去一些「熱鬧」地區
How hot?
有多「熱鬧」？
We talking trigger time?
槍林彈雨？
Sure, if you want.
當然，如果你那麼想
Well, who exactly would I be working for?
好吧，我到底為誰賣命？
The U.S. Government, Jim.
美國政府，吉姆
I want you in Glynco, Georgia next week.
我要你下周去喬治亞州的吉那科
You make it through in one piece,
通過測試
you'll be working Colombia's finest by the summer.
你就可以為哥倫比亞警察工作到夏天
It's just that...
這樣的話…
I'm supposed to get married, sir.
我本打算結婚的，先生
Maybe now is not the time to start a family.
可能現在不是個成家的好時機
We've been together a long time.
我們在一起戀愛多年了
I'm serious about marrying her.
我是真心要取她的
Foreign bride could jeopardize your security clearance.
外籍新娘只會降低你對國家的忠誠
Jim, don't shack up with some Mexican.
吉姆，別和某些墨西哥人同居
Colombian broads are smoking hot and knee deep.
哥倫比亞邊境水深火熱
You get a per diem and a driver.
你會有一個出差津貼和一個司機
You'll live like a fucking king down there.
在那，你可以當個土皇帝
Yes, sir, I understand.
是的，先生，我明白
You take some time,
給你些時間
think about what you want to do.
想想你到底要不要干
This is a serious commitment.
這是個嚴峻的任務
I want the opportunity, sir.
我要這次機會，先生
I want on board.
我入行
Welcome aboard.
歡迎加入
I'm taking a big chance on you.
我給了你一個很大的機會
Thank you, sir.
謝謝，先生
This is the career I've dreamed of.
這正是我夢寐以求的職業
These are your orders,
這些是你的任務
orientation material and travel money.
定位資料和旅途資金
Report to FLETC before the end of working hours Wednesday.
週三下班時間，去聯邦執法培訓中心報道
Thank you, sir.
謝謝
God.
走吧
Sorry, dog.
抱歉， 老兄
I got the job.
我拿到工作了
Oh, shit.
媽的
Yeah?
呀？
Me, too.
我也是
- When do you start? - Monday.
- 你什麼時候開始上班？ - 週一
When do you start?
你什麼時候上崗？
Wednesday.
週三
Big Jim, back on the mars payroll.
吉姆老大， 重新為賺錢奔波咯
Got the W-2
拿到了W- 2
and the employee handbook as proof of employment.
和像工作證一樣的員工手冊
I will be back in the arms of my woman tonight.
我回去要挽著我女人過夜了
Good.
不錯
Hey, we got to celebrate this shit.
嘿，我們媽的要慶祝一下
Salud.
乾杯
Oh, shit.
媽的
Fuzz.
巡警
They're on my ass, dog.
他們在我屁股後面，老兄.
And my license is suspended.
我的駕照已經被吊銷了
Yeah, maybe he's after someone else.
對，他可能跟著其他人
Shit. Fucking shit, man.
媽的，我靠
He's pointing right at me.
他衝著我來的
And we got the open beers.
而且我們啤酒還開著
Fuck the beers, the guns.
該死的啤酒，該死的槍
Shoot the fucker.
打死那混蛋
Car's in my name. We're fucked.
車是我的，我們都要完蛋
Shit. Right when shit was starting to go good, dude,
該死，剛準備一展宏圖，老兄
I'm going to jail.
我就得進監獄
Damn it, I'm going to jail.
該死，要進監獄了
I can dump these guys.
我來對付這些傢伙
Rip the video from their trunk.
避開主幹道上的攝像機
Let's see them hands.
手舉起來！
on the fucking dash!
媽的，舉高點
Grab the sky or I'll blow your fucking heads off.
舉高點不然我打爆你的頭
Blink and die, scumbags.
死的乾脆，混蛋
Oh.
喔
Look who it is, dude.
瞧瞧是誰來了，老兄
It's all right, I know these guys.
沒事了，我認識他們
You fucking asshole.
你他媽的混帳東西
You're such a prick. You scared the fuck out of me.
你嚇的我汗毛直豎
What's up, homie?
怎麼了，兄弟？
- What's up, fool? - What's up, man.
- 什麼情況，笨蛋？ - 夥計，你說呢
I almost shot you, jerk.
我差點開槍打你，笨蛋
That shit wasrt fucking funny, Leo.
可笑的狗屎運，裡奧
Yeah, it was hilarious.
真滑稽
You guys getting fucked up?
你們越來越胡來了
Of course, dog, it's Friday.
當然，老兄，今天週五
Well, Boot, you in the Academy yet?
好吧，兄弟，你進警隊了麼？
Fuck no.
媽的，沒有
Fuck the LAPD.
該死的洛杉磯警局
It's local small-time bullshit.
當地政府盡胡扯
I'm going with the feds.
我將加入聯邦調查局
How'd you get that hook-up, dog?
哪裡來的介紹信，老兄?
You know, me, got my connects, you know.
你知道，我還是有點背景的
Going to FLETC on Wednesday.
週三就去培訓中心了
Hey, see you can get me in there.
嘿，看看能不能也把我弄進去
Yeah, I'll look into that.
好吧，我先進去了再說
How's Sylvia?
西維亞境況可好？
None of your concern, ass wipe.
用不著你操心，管好自己吧
Say hi to her for me, no?
帶我像她問個好，不行麼？
No.
不行
This vato's all protective of his female.
你小子盡藏馬子
Check this out.
瞧瞧這玩意
Nice, huh?
漂亮吧？
It's a nine? Uh-huh.
- 9毫米口徑？ - 恩
Sorry, dog, I got a lot of nines.
抱歉，老兄，9毫米口徑手槍我有不少
Come on, dude, it's a bad-ass Ruger.
拜託，老兄，這把是魯格手槍
Talk to Toussaint. He'll buy that shit.
和圖桑說去 他會買這玩意
Toussaint, he's... he's in Florida.
圖桑， 他…他在佛羅里達
He's back. He called me today.
他回來了 他今天打電話給我了
Page me tonight, bro.
今晚聚會算我個，兄弟
We'll hit the clubs and tear up some fine hinas.
我們還要去查幾個俱樂部，開幾張罰單
Later. Sure, dog.
- 晚些見 - 好的，老兄
I'm on the City's time.
我要去城市巡邏了
You guys be cool.
你個傢伙安分點
Okay?
明白麼？
That fuck... he put a scare in me.
他媽的，他竟敢恐嚇我
Yeah, me, too.
恩，同感
He's a dick.
他是個混蛋
Want to party with him?
難道派對要喊他？
See if this motherfucker's home, dude.
看看這鳥人是否在家
Toussaint? Toussaint?!
圖桑？圖桑？！
Yo, Toussaint?
喲，圖桑？
Yeah, come on, man.
來吧，夥計
Can't go far in that little fucking place of yours.
那麼小的地方你是藏不了的
Goddamnit, I'm coming.
該死的，我來了
Chill out.
冷死啦
Washing that dirty ass.
洗你的髒屁股
Damn it.
媽的
Group love. Group... Come on.
團隊的溫暖，來吧
Group love, boys.
團隊的溫暖，夥計們
Welcome back, hometown.
歡迎回故鄉
Hey, I missed you crazy fuckers, man.
嘿，我想念你個小混蛋
Leo told us you were back.
裡奧告訴我們，你回來了
Thanks for calling asshole.
問候下你的屁股
You a cop?
你當條子了？
Uh-uh. Going federal.
去聯邦調查局
Man, craziest head I know
夥計，我聽過的最瘋狂的事
is going
就是
to be a fed.
做個聯邦探員
Yes, sir! Sir.
是，長官
Still sponging off your woman?
還在吃軟飯？
Fuck you, dog. I got a job.
我靠，老兄，我有工作了
This motherfucker.
你個鳥人
Look, dude.
瞧， 老兄
This is bad.
這太棒了
It's yours for three big ones, dog.
三張大鈔，就是你的了，老兄
Fuck yeah, I want it.
媽的，我要了
What's up?
什麼情況？
Huh?
恩？
What the fuck you say now, huh?
你媽的說什麼，嘿！
Hey. Huh?
嘿，恩？
Bam, bam, bam.
崩，崩，崩
Motherfucker, I'm strapped.
媽的，我身無分文
What the fuck is up now, huh?
他媽的什麼情況？
Whoo-ooh!
呼- 呼！
Whoa, whoa.
哇，哇
Your kneecap and shit.
你這個爛貨
Step up and get blasted.
過來受死吧
Shit, man, what the fuck is up now?
夥計，媽的怎麼辦？
Hey, kick back, gunslinger.
嘿，收回去，槍手
It's loaded.
槍上膛了
That shit goes through walls.
一槍穿牆
You pop the neighbor's little kids.
打你鄰居的小流氓去
Fuck, dude.
媽的， 老兄
Whoa, I'm straight, bro.
喔，我很直率，兄弟
Yo, guys, we got to party tonight, you know?
喲，夥計們，我們今晚有派對
Go clubbir or something.
去俱樂部什麼的地方
I got a better idea.
我有個更好的主意
What?
什麼？
Here, sir.
給，兄弟
Let's go to Mexico.
我們去墨西哥
Mexico?!
墨西哥？！
- Yeah. - I'm in.
- 好的 - 算我一個
Only fags like that...
只有苦力才那麼做
Because you're a little faggot.
因為你是個小同性戀
I don't get it, too much fucking hills.
我才不是，山真他媽多
Right, right.
好的，好的
Dude, yo, dude, stay back boy, stay back.
老兄，喲，老兄， 呆著，夥計，等我
Motherfucker's got to ask permission.
你個鳥人出遊還要拿通行證
Fuck you, all right?
我靠，當然
Let me tell you something.
我告訴你們
I am a grown motherfucking man, all right?
我就是個鳥人
I'm going to tell her the good news,
我去把好消息告訴她
make up, grab my shit and we are out.
做愛，然後我們走人
Excuse me, you're not made out of glass.
對不起，你不是玻璃做的
I'm made out of me.
我就是我
You're drunk.
你喝醉了
I'm celebrating, baby.
我要慶祝下，寶貝
What, another wasted day?
什麼，又虛度了一天？
Here.
看
This is a good company.
這是家不錯的公司
They make all the new condos downtown.
鬧市區的新公寓都是他們造的
How much?
薪水怎樣？
$12 an hour.
每個小時12美金
Plus their MIS guy
而且信息處的那個傢伙 三個月後就要走了
I'm going to update my certifications
我將去升級一下我的證書
and take his job over.
然後就可以接管他的工作了
Then I'll make bank.
這樣我就有錢啦
Such an asshole.
真是混蛋
What? Why? This shit is real.
什麼？這是真的
This is a great job, the pay is outstanding
這是份好工作，薪水也很棒
and it's a great opportunity for me to do what I want to do.
對我來說是個好機會 可以做我想做的事
I know.
我知道
It's so... it's so Mike, you know.
這太…這太「麥克」化了 你知道
You can't just go out and get a shitty job.
你不能就這麼出去幹份垃圾工作
You gotta... you gotta get a...
你應該…，你應該有份…
A dream job?
一份出色的工作？
Yeah, a dream job.
是啊，一份出色的工作
Well, why shouldn't your dream guy have a dream job?
為什麼你出色的男人不該有份出色工作？
Come here, I have a job for you.
過來，我也有份「工作」給你
What the fuck is taking so long?
他媽的怎麼那麼慢？
I knew this shit would happen.
我就知道會這樣的
She hates my ass.
他恨我
She's not going to let him go.
她不會讓他出去的
Go knock.
去敲門
Dude, go knock.
哥們，去敲門
Bro, drag his fucking ass out of there.
兄弟，把那混蛋拖出來
Yo, Miguel.
米蓋爾
Hey.
嘿
Mike, hurry up.
麥克，快點
Yo, what the fuck are you doing?
你他媽在幹嗎？
Come on, dude.
快點，兄弟
Dog, I'm tearir it up, man.
我正爽著呢
I'm hittir it, bro. It's been a few days.
兄弟，我正幹上呢 好多天沒干了
You guys just go ahead, man. I'm gonna chill.
你們去吧，我再爽爽
What?
什麼？
I'm just gonna kick it here with the woman.
我要和我女人做愛
You said you'd go, man.
你說過你會去的
Your womars in your head.
你滿腦子都是你女人
That's wrong.
那不對
She's got your nuts, bro.
她都讓你頭腦發熱了，兄弟
Dog, dog...
哥們，哥們
Sylvia's all happy 'cause I got a job, all right, dude?
我有了工作，西維亞很高興
She wants us to fuckir chill together.
她想要我們在一起
Man, that girl put the zap on your head.
那女人簡直讓你著了魔
This is our last chance to hang.
這是我們最後的機會出去爽了
- You're like my brother. - Yeah.
- 你就像我的親兄弟 - 是啊
You're all I got. You're gonna dog me like that?
你是我的全部 難道你就這樣對待我嗎？
I ain't no fucking do...
我沒那意思
How are you, baby?
你好嗎，寶貝
Hey, Sylvia, he's going to Mexico.
嘿，西維亞 他將要去墨西哥
No, he isn't, Jim. Yes, he is.
- 不，他不會去的，吉姆 - 他會去的
I'm joining the feds. I'm gone, I'm out of here next week.
我要入伍了，我要走了 下個禮拜就會離開這裡
The least you can do
至少你該讓我最好的朋友給我送行
Baby, it's not safe.
寶貝，那兒不安全
All you're going to do is drink.
你們只會去喝酒
Aw, fuck, man.
噢，見鬼
Mike, come on.
麥克，快點
Come on, fuck, man!
兄弟，快點，靠
Come on, you promised.
快啊，你答應過的
You promised, man.
你答應過的，兄弟
Yo... I promised, Sylvia, okay?
我答應過他的，西維亞 行嗎？
Mike, you're not going to Mexico.
麥克，你不能去墨西哥
What?
什麼？
You're not going.
你不能去
I'm not your fucking puppet, Sylvia.
我不是你他媽的木偶，西維亞
All right, you know what, do what you want.
那好，你知道嗎 干你想幹的事去吧
But I'm not going to be here when you get back.
但是當你回來的時候 我已經不在這裡了
That's fucked up.
神經病啊
Why you got to lay that bullshit on him?
為什麼你非要對他這樣？
Because I don't want him going with you, Jim.
因為我不想讓他跟你一起出去，吉姆
You're fucking nuts.
你是個混蛋
You're crazy and you're dangerous,
你是瘋子，而且你很危險
and my biggest nightmare is you with a fucking badge.
我最大的噩夢就是 你居然還是個戴著徽章的警察
You're the last person who should have one.
你根本不配當警察
Yeah? Yeah.
- 是嗎？ - 是的
That's not bullshit, it's the truth.
這不是胡說，是事實
Fuck this!
滾你媽的
Whoa, wait.
等等
Whatever, man.
隨便你，兄弟
Fuckir thanks, homie!
真他媽感謝
Yeah, laters.
好，再見
Bye.
再見
Yo, yo.
喲，喲
I'm going.
我會去的
I gotta go.
我該去
Get the fuck out of here, go!
滾出這裡，滾
Go!
滾
Fuck this shit, man.
靠
Good night, Sylvia.
晚安，西維亞
Kiss my ass, Jim.
親我屁股去吧，吉姆
Oh, any time, sellout.
噢，隨時奉陪，只要你願意
Oh, you going to be happy once he's dead? Huh?
他死了你才開心？
Hey, Toussaint.
嘿，圖桑
I heard the battle, man.
我聽到了一場戰爭啊，兄弟
Yo, your lady didn't want you going, huh?
你女人不讓你出去？
No, but I'm going.
是的，但是我還是要去
- Hell, yeah. - Shit.
- 好極了 - 媽的
- I'm a motherfucking man. - That's right.
- 我是個混蛋 - 沒錯
Shit. I walk the Earth at will.
媽的，我想去哪兒就哪兒
- Damn right. - I do whatever the fuck I want.
- 我想幹嗎就幹嗎
You know, we're men, right?
我們是哥們，對不？
- We're men, right? - That's right.
- 我們是兄弟，對不？ - 沒錯
That's what we do, right?
這就是我們該干的，對不？
Amen. And don't worry...
沒錯！不要擔心
home girl will be right there waiting when you get back.
你回來的時候你女人肯定還在這裡等你
You're right. You're right.
沒錯，沒錯
She wouldn't play that shit like that.
她不會走掉的
Shit, I got a fucking job for real.
媽的，我真的有份工作了
You did.
是啊
Plus you're my homie, dog. You're my homie.
你是我兄弟 是我兄弟啊
You're going to go fucking do your thing
就該為所欲為
- and this is it. - No, shit, dude.
- 現在就是機會 - 沒錯，兄弟
Yo, we're all dogs.
我們都是兄弟
I got you guys back, man.
我支持你們，兄弟
No doubt, no doubt.
毫無疑問，沒的說
It's just going to be fucking cool, yo.
一定會玩的很酷的
I got a job, you got a job.
我有工作了 你也有工作了
Shit, I got some bud.
媽的，我可以搞小妞
- We got some smokes. - We got some
- 我們可以弄些煙 - 我們就要
- motherfucking money. - We are on a mission.
- 他媽的有錢啦 - 我們正在完成使命
Let's get our heads together so we can achieve our objective
讓我們同心協力去完成目標
in a timely manner.
及時順利的去完成目標
Let's get deployed, people.
讓我們行動吧，兄弟們
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
醒醒，醒醒，醒醒
Rise and fucking shine.
太陽他媽的曬屁股了
Come on, ladies. Chow time.
快點，小姐們 吃飯時間到了
Chow's getting cold.
飯都冷掉了
MIKE: Oh, what the fuck, Jim? Chill, dude.
怎麼了，吉姆 別吵，兄弟
Dude, where are we?
兄弟，我們在哪裡？
Family, man.
家裡，哥們
Damn! It's a shizzack...
見鬼，這破地方
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
嘿，嘿，嘿
It's a home, all right?
這是家，知道不？
Respect, bro.
尊重，兄弟
Straighten up, fellas.
站起來，夥計們
My old lady, Marta.
我女人，瑪爾塔
Hola.
你好
Mike. Hola, mucho gusto.
麥克 你好，很高興見到你
Hola, Mike. Toussaint.
- 你好，麥克 - 這是圖桑
Hola. Hola. Hola.
- 你好 - 你好，你好
Hola. Marisa.
這是瑪莉莎
Buenos dias. Mi mama.
- 早上好 - 我媽媽
Mucho gusto. Marta's mom.
- 很高興見到你 - 瑪爾塔的媽媽
Buenos dias.
早上好
Vicki.
- 這是維姬 - 維姬
La prima, esa es mi prima.
這是我妹妹
Mucho gusto.
很高興見到你
Mucho gusto. Mike. Vicki.
- 很高興見到你，我是麥克 - 維姬
Toussaint.
我是圖桑
Vicki.
維姬
Okay. (chuckles)
好
Hey, grab yourselves a rock.
嘿，自己搬塊石頭坐
Si, por favor, sientense.
是的，請坐
MARTA: Vicki?
維姬？
/ Cafe, quieren cafe?
咖啡，要咖啡嗎？
Si, cafe, por favor. Vicki, andale.
是的，咖啡 維姬，拿過來
Tranquila, baby.
安靜，寶貝
Mama!
媽媽
Yeah, w-what's she saying, dude?
她說什麼，兄弟
Oh, they... they think you're cool.
哦，他們認為你很酷
Oh, sweet.
哦，謝謝
Aqui tienes. Gracias.
- 請喝咖啡 - 謝謝
- Caliente. - (whispers): Thank you.
- 熱的
Dude...
兄弟
Marta's fine as fuck, bro.
瑪爾塔幹著一定很爽
Hey, hey, hey...
嘿，嘿，嘿
I'm just saying, dude. You need to marry her, bro.
我只是說說 你應該娶她，兄弟
If you don't, you're a fool.
不娶她你就是笨蛋
/ Que dice?
他說什麼？
Oh...
哦…
- Oh, that shit's good, man. - (Spanish rock song plays)
哦，太美了，兄弟
No shit, you know they got that good fucking weed from here.
沒錯，你知道 他們就是從這裡得到的大麻
That's what I want. Some of that good shit.
這就是我想要的那些好東西
You know where some fields are or something, Jim?
你知道哪裡有嗎，吉姆
Yeah, that's not... I want to see, like, where they grow it.
不是… 我只是想看看它們種在哪裡
You know, and then maybe
你知道，也許…
they'll let us go out and, like, pick some.
他們會讓我們去摘一些
You know, pick some of that really good weed.
摘一些正宗的好貨
Shit.
媽的
MIKE: Toussaint?
圖桑
This is nice.
這裡很漂亮
This is beautiful, man.
這裡太美了，兄弟
Dog, you see this?
哥們，看到沒？
Here.
這裡
Beautiful...
太美了
Man!
哥們
When the hell'd you get all the pistos, dog?
你什麼時候弄到這些的，兄弟？
Mexico, man.
墨西哥，哥們
It's magic.
這裡是魔幻的
TOUSSAINT: He bleed?
他出血了？
JIM: Like a stuffed pig.
象殺頭肥豬一樣
How'd Letty know you were tearing up her sister?
萊蒂是怎麼知道你干她妹妹的？
That fuckir bitch Patti, right?
那個婊子帕蒂，知道不？
- Ah... - I took her to dinner.
- 啊 - 我帶她去吃飯
Took her for a cruise up to Malibu, you know?
帶她去馬裡布，你知道
Got up all in it. Back of my ride...
都是那時搞的 在後座上翻雲覆雨
Pounded that fish, man.
猛搞她
Good fuckir fish.
好爽
I figured the crazy broad
那女人真是太爽了
pulled out some hairs and pubes
我拔掉了她的一些頭髮和趾骨
and stashed it in the seat, you know?
藏在了座位裡
Oh, dude, you got to watch that shit, man.
哦，兄弟，你該看好那女人
Chicks get treacherous.
小妞很容易背叛你
Yeah, no shit. Sibling rivalry, Jim.
是啊，沒錯 同胞鬥爭，吉姆
(chuckles): Next day,
第二天
I'm driving around with Letty all kick back and shit,
我開車和萊蒂出去瘋狂
and she radars in on this rat's nest, man.
她搜索我的車
Pulls out these long-ass hairs, she's like "What are these?"
拉出這些長長的毛髮 問到：「這是什麼？」
"Whose are these?"
「誰的？」
She sees all the pubes mixed in, man... fuckir busted.
她看到還有趾骨混在裡面 真是氣炸了
Busted! (singsong voice): Busted!
爆發了 爆發
Oh!
哦
Dude, how'd she know they were her sister's?
兄弟，她怎麼知道這些就是她妹妹的？
Oh, come on, dude.
哦，得了吧，兄弟
Mexican chick voodoo, right, Mike?
墨西哥小妞都是伏都教 對吧，麥克？
You know, live and learn.
你知道 生活和學習
Yep, next time you'll be all up in your ride
對，下次你就會…
with the Super Vac, dude. Treachery!
被女人背叛了
Yep, treachery.
對，背叛
shouldn't we be
我們不該幫幫她們嗎？
You know how to hand wash?
你知道怎麼洗衣服？
- No. - Then don't sweat it.
- 不知道 - 那麼就別出汗
Yeah, we're men.
是啊，我們是男人
They know we don't do that shit.
他們知道我們不做那種事
That's right.
沒錯
We're men.
我們是男人
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊
This is paradise, huh?
這裡就像是天堂
Yo, Mike?
麥克？
Yeah?
什麼？
They're sending me to Colombia.
他們要把我送到哥倫比亞去
Colombia.
哥倫比亞
Who, the man?
誰，這幫混蛋？
Yep.
對的
They're tearing shit up down there, they need my help.
他們要在那裡掃蕩 他們需要我的幫助
Doing what?
去幹嗎？
Busting up drug labs and drug lords
摧毀那些販毒基地和毒梟
- and all that shit. - You got it.
- 這些屁事 - 說對了
Gonna be an advisor, you know... shoot him, him and him.
會成為一名顧問 殺了這個，那個
Then it's back to the barracks for bitches and beer.
然後回到兵營享受女人和啤酒
I'm set.
我準備好了
Why do you want to do that shit, dude?
你為什麼想幹這種鳥工作，兄弟
I mean...
我意思是…
what about Marta, you know?
瑪爾塔怎麼辦
Ain't gonna happen.
不會有結果的
They told me not to get married.
他們讓我不要結婚
TOUSSAINT: That's messed.
太混蛋了
They really told you that?
他們真的要你別結婚？
Not straight up, but I heard 'em.
沒直說 但我知道是這意思
Yo, if the feds won't let you hook up with your old lady,
如果那幫政府的混蛋 不讓你鉤住自己的女人
you need to tell them to fuck off.
你應該對他們說沒門
Yeah, I mean,
對，我意思是…
you love her, she loves you, right?
你愛她 她愛你，對不？
Dude, you need to move down here, marry Marta,
兄弟，你應該搬到這裡 和瑪爾塔結婚
you know, get a good-ass job
找份好工作
working with fucking tourists or something.
做導遊或是什麼的
Fuck that.
滾你媽的
Taking bucket baths in cold-ass water?
難道讓他們在這冷水裡洗澡？
You know, wading around in ankle-deep mud?
在只有膝蓋深的水裡游泳？
Outhouses, man!
不可能，兄弟
Fuckir outhouses!
沒門
You told Marta yet?
你告訴瑪爾塔沒？
You love this place.
你愛這個地方
It's in your eyes, man.
都在你的眼裡，兄弟
Dude, this is what it's all about.
兄弟，這就是全部
You got a woman that loves you and a place to stay.
你有個愛你的女人 有個居住的地方
You'd be happy here, and you know it.
你會在這裡過的幸福的 你知道的
Yeah, well, shacking up with Marta,
是啊，和瑪爾塔同居
squeezing out some puppies, has its appeal, but...
然後生幾個小孩 確實很吸引人，但是…
this is my career.
這是我的職業
I got one shot.
我要去幹
You're making a mistake.
你做出了錯誤的決定
You should stay right here with your lady.
你應該留下來和你女人在一起
What the fuck you gonna do
你去哥倫比亞幹嗎？
Whack people,
重擊敵人
program shit.
鳥屁訓練
You ain't down, fuck you.
你不懂的，滾你的
Bring in my gunships
開著武裝直升機
and smoke your little jungle hideaway. You know?
把叢林裡的敵人藏身處炸爛
I mean, I'm a solider of the apocalypse, man.
我意思是 我是啟示錄裡的一名戰士
I'll be in a chopper,
我會成為切割機一樣
door-gunning villagers and shit. Fuck 'em.
掃蕩村莊
Kill the chickens and dogs, too, man.
殺死雞狗
I don't give a fuck.
想殺就殺
Yeah.
是嗎
MIKE: Doce anos.
12年
- Doce anos. - JIM: Doce anos...
- 12年
Doce... we've been together that long.
我們在一起已經那麼長了
Es muy bonita.
很漂亮
Man, you're bring sand to the beach, dumb ass.
兄弟，你這是自討苦吃
- Cover that shit up. - TOUSSAINT: Jim, dude!
- 蓋起來 - 吉姆，哥們
Huh?
啊？
How you say, um, "You're beautiful" in Spanish?
西班牙語「你很漂亮」怎麼說？
Huh? "Bonita." Bonita.
- 啊？「波尼塔」 - 波尼塔
Come on, you don't know that shit, Toussaint?
得了，你連這都不會說，圖桑？
Tu... bonita.
你…漂亮
VICKl: Gracias.
謝謝
MIKE: Hey, baby, see my new one?
嘿，寶貝，看到我的新歡沒？
- Right, did I get it? - Huh?
- 我說的對嗎？ - 啊？
Think I got it?
我說對了嗎？
Yeah, she got the point.
是的，她懂你意思了
Yo, Mike, that chick digs you.
麥克，那小妞在勾引你
What chick?
什麼小妞
MIKE: Oh, she's good, dog.
那小妞不錯
Yeah, name's Lila.
是啊，她叫莉拉
She's a freak. She'll fuck you, dude.
是個變態 她會把你搞死的，兄弟
She's a freak, huh?
她是變態？
How you know? You fuck her?
你怎麼知道？你幹過她？
No, out of respect for Marta.
沒，不是我不想…
Not that I don't want... Hey, baby.
嘿，寶貝
Ask her to dance.
請她跳舞
I'm not cheating on Sylvia, dude.
我不會做對不起西維亞的事的
There's a big gap between dancing and fucking, man.
上床和跳舞那是兩碼事
Go explore it.
去探索一下
No shit.
好
No.
不
You're fucking nuts.
你他媽是混蛋
You fucked up, woman.
你這笨女人
I'll do it.
我會殺了你
It's easy.
這很容易
Jim!
吉姆
What's up, man, huh?
怎麼回事，兄弟，啊？
Where's Toussaint?
圖桑在哪裡？
He's dancing.
他在跳舞
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 是嗎？ - 是的
- You gonna get back
你要回到聚會上去？
to the party? - Yeah.
是的
Let's get back to the party, man.
讓我們回到聚會裡去
- Yeah. - Hey, uh, go,
- 是 - 嘿，去
go tell Toussaint that
去告訴圖桑
we're gonna get the fuck out of here, man.
我們要走了
Just go into the party, tell him we're gonna go.
去聚會裡告訴他
We're leaving, huh?
我們就走？
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna leave.
是啊，是啊，我們要走了
Let's go, yeah?
我們走
Yeah, let's go.
是的，我們走
Go ahead, go get Toussaint, man.
去，去找圖桑
Go get him.
去找他
Hey, we're going.
嘿，我們要走了
Come on.
快點
Fuck you, dude.
滾你媽的
I'm having a great time, bro.
我正玩得爽呢，兄弟
Then walk back to L.A., motherfucker.
那你就走回洛杉磯吧，混蛋
You're in the car or not.
上車還是不上
He's fucking crazy, man. What the fuck!
他是個瘋子 真他媽
All right, let's go, man.
好，我們走
Hey, yo, what the fuck is your problem, psycho?!
嘿，你怎麼回事，神經病
Hey, hey, homeboy's losing it, all right?
他失控了，知道不
Shut the fuck up and just get in the car, all right?
閉嘴，坐進車裡
Fucking bullshit!
真他媽混蛋
TOUSSAINT: Fucked up!
混蛋
Dude, dude... dude, slow down.
兄弟，兄弟，慢點
Fuck, man.
靠
Whoo, yeah, man.
哇，哥們，爽
Slow down, you crazy motherfucker!
慢點 你這混蛋
I want a cop to pull me over.
我想找個警察飆車
JIM: Treachery.
叛徒
Fucking treachery.
真他媽叛徒
Jim, slow down!
吉姆，慢點
Shut up!
閉嘴
Fuck, dude.
靠，兄弟
Only female I trust.
我相信的唯一一個女人
Fuck you, God!
滾你媽的上帝
You ain't got the fucking balls to take my ass.
你這個沒睪丸的
Jim, don't say that shit, dude.
吉姆，不要這麼說
Jim!
吉姆
Dude, you are getting out of control, okay?
兄弟，你失控了，知道不
You need psychiatric help, man.
你需要心理治療
You're seriously fucked up, dude.
你已經嚴重混亂了，兄弟
All right, you need to sue the military or something.
對的，你應該去起訴他們的軍事行動
You used to be mellow.
你以前很成熟的
Later, homie.
再見
'Night, dog.
晚安，哥們
Dude, I ain't hanging around you anymore
兄弟，我不再跟你混了
until you get some fucking help.
除非你去看一下醫生
You can 12-step off, bitch.
你可以退避三舍，婊子
You're dismissed.
你被開除了
He's right, dude.
他說的對，兄弟
Yeah.
是啊
Georgia will get me squared away.
佐治亞會把我的一切整頓好的
Hope so.
希望如此
What was that shit with Marta, dude?
他媽的你跟瑪爾塔是怎麼回事？
I don't know why that happened.
我不知道為什麼會那樣
But I'm cool. I'm cool now.
但是我現在冷靜了 現在冷靜了
Okay?
好？
Yeah.
好
I'm cool.
現在我冷靜了
Look, dude, she told me she was pregnant.
聽著，哥們 她告訴我她懷孕了
I had a panic attack.
我當時真是氣炸了
I pulled my gun.
我拔出我的槍
Come on, dog,
得了吧，哥們
I thought you loved her, dude.
我還以為你真的愛她呢
I do.
我確實愛她
God, fuck.
天那，我靠
Come on, man, let's go drop off that bud.
好，哥們，我們去送貨
What bud?
什麼貨
There's 20 kilos in the trunk.
行李箱裡有20公斤
Say that again?
你說什麼？
There's 20 kilos in the trunk, man.
行李箱裡有20公斤，哥們
- Of weed? - Yeah.
- 大麻？ - 是的
Get the fuck out of here, man.
他媽的快離開這裡
I picked it up at the party.
我聚會的時候搞的
I'm dropping it at Casper's.
我送到卡斯波那裡去
Casper's?
卡斯波？
(laughing): I get three Gs.
能賺三千塊啊
We get three Gs.
我們能賺三千塊啊
You drove it across the border?
你帶著貨穿過了邊境？
(laughing): Yeah.
是啊
What if they would've caught us?
如果他們抓到我們怎麼辦？
Couldrt happen, man.
不可能的，兄弟
My shit is on fire right now, man.
我已經準備好了傢伙
My shit is wired
我的神經正緊繃著呢
You risked my ass without telling me?
你不告訴我就拿我的命去冒險？
That's not cool, man. For three fucking Gs?
那並不好玩，兄弟 就為了三千塊？
That's... that's a good rate for transporting that.
運這個賺頭不小
Shit, if I'd told you,
媽的，如果我告訴了你
you would have gotten
你會在邊境那裡露餡的
all fucking hinkey at the border, man, gotten us nabbed.
會害的我們都被抓
I wouldn't have been in the fucking car, dude!
我不該上你車的
I would've been on motherfucking Greyhound.
我寧願乘長途汽車
That's a serious breach of the homie code, man,
這可是重罪
not fuckir telling me.
居然不告訴我
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry, you know.
對不起，兄弟 對不起
I should've had... I should've got you guys,
我本該…
you know, walk across the border.
我本該讓你們走路穿過邊境的
I could've met you somewhere.
然後可以在某地碰面
But, you know, I got bills, I got shit.
但是，你知道，我要過日子
I gotta put my shit in storage.
我不得不儲備點貨
I gotta get gas out to Georgia.
我要加油去佐治亞
Oh, fuck your money woes, dog!
哦，滾你媽的錢錢錢
I am not catching a fuckir case for you.
我不想為了你惹上官司
Let me out of the fucking car right now.
讓我現在就下車
Fuck, man. Come on, man, let's drop this shit off.
靠，兄弟，行了 讓我們把貨送走
Let's get paid!
拿到錢
Let me out right here.
現在就讓我下車
Mi-Mi-Mi-Mike! Listen, listen!
麥克，麥克 聽著，聽著
Let me out right here, right now!
讓我在這裡下車 現在！
You will feel so much better with a fistful of twenties.
當你有了錢，那感覺多好啊
Huh?
啊？
Dude, we're drunk,
兄弟，我們都喝了酒
and we got a trunk full of fuckir weed, dude, I am not...
而且我們有一行李箱的大麻
Okay, fuckir, Mike, don't bitch out on me!
靠，麥克 別對我發火
Don't fucking bitch out on me!
不要發火
I am still on probation, dick head.
我還在假釋期，豬頭
Let me out now!
讓我下車
Let me out right here right fuckir now, dude!
馬上
Let me get paid, will you?
讓我先拿到錢，好不？
Will you fuckir let me get paid?!
你先讓我拿到錢，好不？
Oh, yo, get paid, man.
哦，去拿錢把
Fuckir go for it, all right?
去拿錢，好吧？
Just let me get the fuck out. I don't give a fuck, dude.
先讓我下車 我不稀罕那錢
What the fuck are you doing, man?
你他媽幹嗎？
are you doing, Jim?
你他媽在幹嗎，吉姆
What the fuck?
幹嗎
Fuck you!
滾你媽
Fuck, I'm sorry, dude,
靠，對不起，兄弟
I'm sorry, dude.
對不起，兄弟
Okay? I'm sorry.
好嗎？我對不起你
Why the fuck did you put a gun to my head?
為什麼你他媽用槍指著我？
Huh?
啊？
You gonna shoot me?
你要殺了我嗎？
No, man. I'm sorry. I was trippir.
不，兄弟，對不起 我發暈了
I'd never...
我從沒…
I'd never put a fuckir gun to your head, dude
我從沒用槍指著你的腦袋，兄弟
I know.
我知道
I know you wouldn't, man. I'm sorry.
我知道你不會的 對不起
First your lady, now me, man. What the fuck is up?
先是你女人，現在是我 你他媽到底怎麼回事？
I'm not thinking.
我沒法思考
I got too much shit going on.
我腦子發暈了
Oh, fuck, I'm just faded, man, that's all.
哦，媽的，我只是頭腦發熱 就這樣
I'm just fuckir fade right now, okay?
我只是頭腦發熱
I'll cruise you by your pad.
我等會兒送你回家
I'll drop you off, man.
我會送你回去的，兄弟
I'm sorry.
對不起
Yeah. You're a fuck-up.
是啊，你是個混蛋
I'm going with you so you don't fuck this shit up, too.
我和你一起去 這樣你就不會把這事搞砸了
We'll go to Casper's... get the money.
我們一起去卡斯波那裡 去拿錢
Yeah.
是啊
Then you can drop me off home,
然後你送我回家
you can go to Georgia fed out and be the fuckir man.
你可以去佐治亞 去做你的混蛋士兵
Yeah, I'm gonna be the fucking man.
是啊，我會去做混蛋士兵
I can drop you off, you know.
我可以送你回去
Take you up the hill.
送你回山上
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不
No.
不
Keep on going.
繼續開
MIKE: Looks sketchy.
好像沒人
JIM: I don't know.
我不知道
Ho, what, you gonna shoot their pigeons?
什麼？你想射死他們的鴿子？
Yeah.
是
Just hurry up.
快點
Yo, Casper!
卡斯波
Buenos noches, senor.
晚上好，老人家
/ Tiene lose cosatles?
有貨嗎？
Go pop the trunk, dude.
去打開行李箱，兄弟
Con permiso.
拿出來
What's up, Casper?
近況如何，卡斯波？
What up, Jim?
你怎麼樣，吉姆？
What's crackir, man.
什麼情況，兄弟
Is that you, Mike?
是你嗎，麥克？
Whassup, homes?
怎麼樣，兄弟
Yo, Casper. What up, dog?
卡斯波 近況怎樣，哥們
Nothing, homey. How you been?
沒什麼，哥們 近況還好嗎？
Still with Sylvia?
還和西維亞在一起？
Hope so.
希望如此
Gonna find out tonight.
今晚就知道了
So whassup with your brother, dog?
你兄弟怎樣？
Fernie?
菲尼？
Got blasted by the hulas awhile back, ese.
被陷害死了
Damn.
該死
Sorry to hear that, dog.
很遺憾
You play, you pay.
玩火者必自焚
He knew what time it was.
他知道時刻到了
Right.
沒錯
Hey, we gotta bounce.
嘿，我們要走了
You got the money?
你帶錢了嗎？
Yeah, just let me check the shit, okay?
帶了，讓我檢查一下這貨 好嗎？
Yo, bring the feria, homey!
把錢拿過來
How's your old lady?
你女人怎樣？
Eh... bitch finally graduated, yo.
啊，那婊子終於畢業了
JIM: Oh, fuck it!
哦，媽的
CASPER: Yeah, now she can support my ass, eh?
是啊，現在她可以養我了
FLACO: I got all the feria right here, dog.
所有的錢都在這裡了
It's all rolled up and shit.
都捲好了
You know what I mean?
你知道我意思嗎？
Ready to go, dog. Check this out, homes.
準備走人，哥們 看一下錢
Ah, hell, nah!
啊
CASPER: Yo, hold up, dog. Don't trip.
等等 別頭腦發熱
I know these fools. They're with me, ese.
我認識這些傢伙 他們和我一起的
These are the fools that jacked me, man!
就是這幫混蛋玩了我
Fuck these motherfuckers! I'm shooting both of 'em!
這幫混蛋 我要都殺了他們
At least give the homeboy a pass right here, dog.
至少讓他先走
Yeah, yeah, let him bounce.
好，好 讓他先走
I don't give a fuck.
我才不管
I want this white boy in a box, though.
我要殺了這個傢伙
Hey, you in the ride.
嘿，車上的傢伙
I ever see you again, ese, you best be
要是我下次再看到你
getting your last supper, 'cause you're a dead man.
我就殺了你
Hey, just get the fuck outta here, Mike.
嘿，快離開這裡，麥克
JIM: Take off, homey.
走吧，兄弟
I'll be cool.
我沒事的
What the fuck?
他媽的
Don't trip, ese. I'm cool.
不要發暈，兄弟 我很冷靜
Chill, dog! Chill, dog!
冷靜，兄弟
I got three kids... (body thuds)
我還有三個孩子
LIL' CHUCKY: Oh, no, please, sir! Please!
哦，不，求求你 先生，求求你
- No, no, no, no, no! - MIKE: Jim, no!
- 不，不，不，不 - 吉姆，別
Please, please.
求求你，求求你
Why the fuck did you do that?
你他媽都幹了些什麼
JIM: Pull the door!
關門
- (engine rewing) - Oh, my God, Jim!
哦，天那，吉姆
I'm hit bad.
我被擊中了
What have we done?
我們都做了些什麼啊
I can't move my arm... and I can't feel my legs!
我的手不能動了 我感覺不到我的腿
I can't move shit.
我不能動了
I'm fucked up.
我完蛋了
MIKE: Okay...
沒事
Don't trip...
挺住
Don't trip, dog.
挺住，兄弟
County Hospital's right there.
醫院就在前面
No! No! No! County Hospital...
不，不，不
Don't you dare take me there!
不要送我去醫院
Don't you dare!
你敢！
I'm not going out like that.
我不會去的
No, we're going. No, no...
不，我們要去 不，不…
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we're going.
不，不，不，不 不，我們要去
No medical treatment.
不要去醫院 不去醫院
But, but...
但是，但是…
(gasping): Mike, Mike...
麥克，麥克
You gotta kill me.
你該殺了我 你殺了我吧
Why? Why?
為什麼？為什麼？
I fucked up.
我完蛋了
Everything's shitty.
什麼都完了
No, no...
不，不
Mercy kill me.
送我上路吧
Ah... ah, please, mercy kill me.
求你 送我走吧
Ah, oh, no, dude.
啊，不，不，兄弟
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不 不，不，不
No, everything's gonna be fine.
不，一切都會好起來的
Jim, shh-shh, shh-shh, shh-shh, shh-shh.
吉姆，噓 噓，噓
Everything's gonna be fine.
一切都會好起來的
Take a look at me, you dumb fuck!
看看我 你這笨蛋
Everything's gonna be fine?!
一切會好起來？
Come on...
快點
You take my piece...
拿我的槍
and you put it to my fuckir head...
對著我的腦袋
and you pull the trigger.
扣動扳機
You fuckir step up...
你他媽的快點
No...
不
...and you do it.
照我說的做
'Cause I can't.
我不能
(sobbing): Don't be a fuckir pussy.
不要像個小女人
Oh, my God...
哦，我的天那
Don't think about it.
別猶豫了
Huh?
啊？
Do it.
快點
Please.
求你了
Just kill you and bail?
就這麼殺了你然後走掉？
Yeah.
對
Just take off.
殺了就走
And don't look back...
不要回頭
or you'll...
否則你會…
or you'll turn into a pillar of salt.
否則你會沒命的
Hey... Hey...
嘿…嘿
you wanted to know what it was like to kill someone.
你不是一直想體驗殺人的感覺嗎
What's up, huh?
怎麼啦，啊？
No one's gonna know.
沒人會知道的
Hmm?
嗯？
Just you...
只有你
and just me.
還有我
And God.
還有上帝
No fuckir way.
他媽的沒門
- Huh? - No fuckir way.
- 啊？ - 他媽的沒門
You're crazy; I'm not shootir you, dog.
你瘋了 我不會殺你的
It's mercy, dog.
成全我，兄弟
It's mercy.
成全我
I deserve that.
我罪有應得
I'd do it for you.
是你的話，我也會殺了你的
Yeah.
嗯
Take it.
拿著
Yeah, yeah.
快，快
D-Don't, don't think about it.
不要…不要猶豫
Don't think about it.
不要猶豫不決
Yeah, yeah...
對，對
Ah, yeah.
嗯，對
Yeah.
對
Ah... ah...
啊…啊
You did this to yourself, you stupid fuck!
都是你自找的 你這混蛋
You're always doing stupid shit!
你總是干蠢事
- I gotta fuckir fix it! - Okay, okay.
- 我不得不來幫你了斷 - 好，還
Is that what you fuckir want?!
這就是你想要的嗎？
- Yes. - Huh?
- 是 - 啊？
You want me to fuckir fix your head,
你想要我殺了你
- once and for all?! - Come on, it's easy.
- 一了百了？ - 快點，很容易的
It's easy. No! Bullshit!
- 很容易 - 不，胡說
Bullshit! Not for me!
胡說，對我不簡單
I love you, fuckir shit bag.
我愛你，笨蛋
I love you, too.
我也愛你
I'm gonna miss you, brother.
我會想你的，兄弟
I'm sorry.
對不起
- Everything's gonna be okay. - Yeah.
- 一切都會好的 - 是啊
Yeah.
是啊
I know.
我知道